Chapter 35: The True Return of Lord Salazar Slytherin

I would like to thank Kuilin, my beta.

4:29 pm, July 14th, 1993

While packing his things for his upcoming trip for Ukraine the next morning in his suitcase-bedroom, a sudden sense of approaching danger prompted Severus to reach for his wand, and to activate the defensive magical items on himself. However, before Severus' bright blue Protego Vitamaxima shield was properly raised, a red bolt of light shattered the forming blue hemisphere and hit Severus.

"Better, but not enough." A comment came from an invisible old man.

With a wave of daze associated with memory charms, Severus began to recognize the speaker, for the eleventh time. The dark-haired wizard swayed a little bit, grunted inside, and remembered where he was planning to go this very afternoon: South Africa.

-Because even Lord Salazar Slytherin found it was almost impossible to sneak into the Room of Requirement and use the Stone without anyone knowing. Hooray, Mad-Eye!

"Am I passable for the role?" Salazar revealed himself in front of Severus, and asked.

Severus noticed that Salazar even managed to slip some Afrikaans accent into his South African English, and was secretly astonished by the ancient lord for his amazing speed at learning new languages.

-At the age of one hundred and fifty, yet he learned the simple verbal parts of a new language within two to three weeks! Well, perhaps this isn't particularly surprising for someone like Salazar Slytherin, or Albus Dumbledore. Those lords all master hundreds of languages. I have such a long way to go.

The linguistic question aside, Severus examined his ancient ancestor's appearance closely, and determined that Salazar's clothes tonight was passable for a dejected fifty-something South Africa wizard clinging desperately on old glories: outdated wizarding robes that were a bit too tight, made with fine material, yet the elegance of the robes was marred by signs of wear and tear; dragon-hide boots that had been fashionable some twenty years ago, now spotted with slouchy attempts to magically repair the patches of ruptured leather; an ancient-looking snake shaped brooch that was carefully cleaned, which could easily be considered as a family heirloom.

Severus silently commented: nowadays, what kind of wizard wears brooch besides one Lucius Malfoy? But this suits the snobbish character Salazar is going to play quite well. By the way, certain characteristics of Salazar suits his role quite well, too.

Severus hissed, "Yess."

Salazar nodded, grabbed Severus, applied concealing charms on both of them, and activated a portkey that could only be made by someone with higher security clearance level than the current headmistress.

A portkey and several Apparitions later, Severus and Salazar landed at the supposed residence of one Claudius Gamp, a laughingstock in the South African wizarding society after Severus sabotaged his final grand show in his haughty and pathetic life.

Around this time of 1992, the Ministry of Magic of South Africa welcomed its first black minister, plus eleven more black high-rank officials. A number of white wizards were quite unhappy about this change in the predominately white ministry, and about similar changes that was taking place in the Muggle side of the country. Amongst the racist wizards was one Claudius Gamp. Although the Gamp family began to go downhill over thirty years ago, the last Scion of the Gamp House still reasoned that his failure was entirely due to the rise of black wizards. After imbibing too much alcohol into his system in a bar with a dozen or so other white supremacists, Claudius announced to the cheering crowd that he would sacrifice his life in a ritual to bring South Africa back to its course. When Claudius staggered out of the bar, Severus secretly followed him, interrupted the sacrificial ritual which, according to Severus' estimation, would only blow up the Gamp House and things within a mile. Besides saving possibly several hundred Muggles in the nearby village, Severus mercifully helped Claudius to think that he had accomplished his plan, while he actually only managed to achieve part of it - which was, of course, the suicide part.

On the third day, Claudius returned to that bar in the form of a brown pebble in Severus' box, while polyjuiced Severus was mocked by Claudius' obnoxious friends, who were too cowardice to actually do anything themselves, yet felt perfectly entitled to jeer the one who had claimed to do something.

-Maybe they are just in need of a dark lord with passable motivation skills to actually start something.

Severus made a sarcastic mental note to himself, and staged a spectacular fist fight with Claudius' friends for being insulted. After Severus landed several of the highly incompetent wizards into Cape Town Magical Hospital for bruises, Severus successfully made sure that the poor brown pebble in his box lost his remaining social ties.

Nowadays, Severus just needed to occasionally sell some of Claudius' old clothes and family collections, and to place some large owl orders of Firewhiskey afterwards to make this identity alive in the eyes of the magical world.

Needless to say, it took Severus quite some efforts to find and obtain this convincing false identity, yet the powerful magic that Salazar already gave him hints on really paid off for Severus' best cover. Moreover, if it were not for the ancient-looking scrolls fabricated by the authentic medieval wizard, and the hints he left in Severus' mind, Severus and Mad-Eye might still be busy trying various wild ideas proposed by the Boy-Who-Lived in front of the Mirror this very day.

Severus did hold some small grudges toward Salazar over one of his hints. Severus knew that Salazar only left him the idea that he should try to probe the procedures of people being transported to the Hospital. Salazar had never indicated in any way or form that Severus should endanger Draco in doing so. However, Severus still ended up giving Mad-Eye a chance to do things to Draco. Severus knew the young Malfoy brat needed to encounter some real danger to get rid of his illusion and contempt of false safety created by pureblood security protocols, yet Severus should use one of his own "kill-a-pureblood-creatively" methods, instead of handing Mad-Eye the opportunity that the old Auror had definitely yearned for in the past one hundred years. Severus knew it was unfair to blame Salazar for the affair, which only proved what a horrible godfather Severus was, yet Severus couldn't help.

In front of his clear failure as a godfather, Severus didn't want to put too much emphasis on the bit of success he had. Severus managed to slip a note to his subconscious thoughts before Salazar temporarily blocked his memory by the end of their second meeting, in which he told himself that he needed to teach Draco how to become an animagus very quickly.

A few days later, although several hundred pieces of undisclosed gold donated to the Department of Magical Law Enforcement ensured that Draco would never be charged for the offense, the new Lord Malfoy had become a criminal in the eyes of magical Britain, for the offense of being an illegal animagus.

Severus amused himself each time he thought of his godson's animagus form: one can hardly believe how attached that boy is to his snake-ish Father - the boy with a name of dragon and wyvern symbols on his pajamas became a snakedragon, a hybrid between a wyvern and a snake! And the endless not-so-subtle gloats from Lucius, simply unbearable! I wonder, if I should thank Merlin that Draco's animagus form doesn't have blue stripes. True, this rare form of animagus did solve the problem of Parseltongue, snakedragon hide and scales are resistant to a lot of curses, its fangs contain deadly poisons similar to that of basilisks, the body is resistant to most poisons and infections, and it can fly pretty fast, yet the twenty-foot long creature with shining light-gold colored scales is hardly any form of hiding.

-Hopeless Malfoy show-offs!

Moreover, Severus could hardly suppress his smile each time he thought of the snakedragon's funny Parseltongue accent due to his dragon part, where a "yesss" would become a "yesshh", and "ssit" would turn into "sshhit".

It seemed that Salazar had not realized that neither the Malfoys nor Severus were natural Parselmouths, and Severus didn't plan to do anything that might lessen Lord Slytherin's grandfatherly thoughts on the younger Malfoy – after Salazar learned that Draco couldn't even master ancient Greek, the old lord blamed Lucius for Draco's poor accent and substandard linguistic education in general, and he had planned to teach Draco himself when he had time, which worked exactly according to Severus' plan. And for some strange reason that Severus didn't really want to ponder upon, after discovering that Severus was not a stutter in modern English, Salazar also blamed Lucius for not providing Severus proper private linguistic education, and began to teach Severus the correct ways to move his tongues and vocal cords in Parseltongue.

Severus was sure poor old Lucius would understand. To be honest, the imaginary scene of a teeth-gritting Lucius reluctantly thanking the unkempt half-blood for getting his son a great tutor offered Severus endless entertainment.

Entertainment and annoyance that were commonly associated with the Malfoys aside, Severus knew the advantages he gained from Salazar all required payment. And if Severus wanted Salazar to continue his grandfatherly feelings towards Draco, Severus probably needed to pay for Draco's share as well, in which providing Salazar with a proper false identity was the least he could do.

For their plan to work, Salazar needed more than a false identity, proper garments and phrasing in commonly used sentences. Salazar needed to be able to act the role of an obnoxious twentieth century wizard, and that had proved to be the difficult part.

The wizarding world had moved slower than the Muggle world during the past several hundred years, however, there was still no way that Severus and Plumpton's portrait could teach Salazar everything about the twentieth century within a few days. Severus could make sure that Salazar wasn't too surprised when he encountered a wizarding radio or a magical moving photo, and the ancient lord was quick in picking up the proper use of current dining utensils, yet it was impossible for Severus to introduce something such as toilet tissues that was so common for him that he didn't even consider the need for explanation.

"This rolled parchment is so soft and þynne. What skin is it made from? Why do you put such things in the toilet?" Salazar had once asked.

Then Severus began to explain that "þynne" was pronounced as "thin" these days, and since current Muggles and wizards used chopped wood to make paper, paper became so cheap that people even used paper for bathroom needs.

"Interesting. I have heard -" Salazar paused, then hissed, "what iss the current pronunciation for Chinesse?"

Here was when Severus drew out a map and named every major country in the world to Salazar. Then one question led to another, and Severus ended up explaining the prominent wizarding schools founded after Salazar's time, drew out his collection of Uagadou, A History, and showed Salazar the moving pictures of the headmaster and professors during Claudius' school years in Uagadou School of Magic.

"Oh, and the admission letters to the school are by a dream messenger. As far as I have heard, the dream messenger put a token into your hand while you were sleeping some night between your eleventh birthday and the start date of the school year." Severus showed Salazar the well-kept token he found at the Gamp House. "Moreover, both English and French were used as teaching languages in Uagadou, and blacks and whites were separated into different classes back when you were a student."

Severus twisted his lips in disapproval, and continued, "Culture wise, it is noteworthy that although we British abolished slavery almost two hundred years ago, and Shacklebolt is even considered as a Noble and Most Ancient House, it is not the case in every part of the world, especially, not in Africa. I suppose, the adoption of Muggle racism among the white wizards migrating to Africa was somewhat understandable, because they needed some kind of moral justifications for colonialism, and few people wanted to consider themselves as the bad guys. Going back to your education, since you were educated in the White-English House, in which the majority of your classmates were white, - except one Japanese and two Indians, who were honorary whites, - the majority of your supposedly classmates were descendants of British colonists. The majority of them were only racist, not blood purists; since you were both a racist and a blood purist, and never hesitated before voicing your viewpoints, you were not that popular at school. Here is Claudius' school yearbook - lucky that they have these in Uagadou, otherwise, it's hard to find the names and faces. Oh, and this girl, Claudius still kept some love letters from her, let me get the letter..."

It took Severus four five-hour time-turned sessions to cover the basics that Salazar might encounter en route to the Hospital as Claudius Gamp.

Then, the two ex-Heads of Slytherin House spent quite some time in and around Cape Town Magical Hospital to observe how patients were diagnosed and transported to the only real Hospital in the world. Things there appeared to be quite similar to what Severus observed one year ago: the hostility between whites and blacks, and the rift between wizards of British descendance and that of Dutch descendance, had made South African wizarding society extremely convenient for outside wizards with unspeakable motives. The safety rules were intentionally badly made, and even more poorly observed; communication between different departments in the hospital and the ministry was somewhere between highly ineffective and nonexistence; English-speaking wizards and Afrikaans-speaking wizards stabbed each other's back even if the very act might result in their own injuries as well; white officials who thought they were soon to be replaced by blacks could be easily bought, while the newly elected black officials didn't hold any better ethics than their white colleagues.

Two five-hour sessions later, Lord Slytherin announced his conclusion: "A nation so divided can easily be conquered, even by you, Severus."

Severus wasn't so sure this was meant to be a compliment. However, there was something quite worrisome that he needed to tell Salazar: "Be warned, Muggless in thiss nation have masss-ssacrifice v-weaponss, ass you call them."

"What?!" The aged lord hissed in utter disbelief. "If the Muggless run their government like thiss, we sshall all be desstroyed by the weaponss!"

Severus then explained a piece of good news: "Other Muggle nations, such as the United States and Russia, are doing one good thing: they are pressuring South Africa to give up their nuclear weapons. From what I recently read, the South Africans are cooperating, or at least, they seem so."

"We should make them so. From what we know, the wizards protecting the Muggle officials should be easily bought or deceived." Lord Slytherin decided. "Is there any other Muggle nation that can be easily disarmed?"

Severus smiled a sly smile: "Ukraine, and some other former Soviet states."

Salazar raised one eyebrow, and smirked, "Sseveruss, you are truly my desscendant."

Hence, Severus gained himself a very powerful ally for his trip to the former Soviet states, that was, of course, if their plan for today would be successful.

Severus eyed his ancient ancestor, and nervously watched as the aged lord downed several bottles of age-reducing potion that made him look as if he was in his early thirties. Although the age-reducing potion couldn't really put youth back to organs and joints that had deteriorated over time, it could safely change one's appearances. And since this was one of the most commonly used potions among the idiots who transfigured themselves, it was OK for Salazar to have some as well.

In the second step, the original Lord Salazar Slytherin needed to look like a stupid wizard who wanted his looks to resemble Salazar Slytherin. Since polyjuice potion would definitely be one of the first things Mad-Eye might check for in the Hospital, the two ex-Heads of Slytherin House didn't plan to use polyjuice potion to make Salazar resemble Claudius. Instead, they used non-free human transfiguration, and they needed to intentionally make the work sloppy, such as changing Salazar's hair color to somewhere between brown and black, his face unevenly pointed, and several scars and moles on the original Claudius' body badly masked. With the combined efforts of Salazar and Severus, this was easily done.

Third, since neither Salazar nor Severus trusted the healers in the emergency room in Cape Town Magical Hospital, they agreed that free transfigurations on the vital organs and joints should be only conducted by themselves. After practicing free human transfiguration extensively on Lucius, Severus was relatively good at this. Unfortunately, they needed to make the work sloppy in the eyes of the inexperienced. Therefore, during their previous five-hour session, Severus taught everything he knew about free human transfiguration to Salazar, and left the practice to be "sloppy" part to the aged lord. For what was worse, since they couldn't appear to be too powerful, the time span that the free transfigurations could sustain was limited to one and a half hours.

Severus glanced at his mechanical watch, which showed "4: 58", and nodded to Salazar. The two ex-Heads of Slytherin House quickly started their free transfigurations, with Severus doing the first round of transfiguration, while Salazar checking Severus' work, and making modifications.

About fifteen minutes later, they were ready to move to the Cape Town Magical Hospital.

Severus disillusioned himself, pulled on Salazar's invisibility cloak, applied several one-sided sound and smell concealing charms, then Apparated to Cape Town Magical Hospital, where Salazar would separately Apparate to.

In front of the hospital's recipient desk, Salazar proudly announced to the waiting crowd in lines: "Today, the world will witness the return of Lord Salazar Slytherin, the greatest wizard after Merlin."

Everyone looked at Salazar as if he was mad.

Then, Salazar waved a page he teared from Hogwarts, A History, which showed the sculpture of Salazar Slytherin in the Slytherin dungeons. "Don't I look exactly like the great wizard?"

The crowd sniggered, and started not-exactly whispering to each other.

"Another standard idiot."

"Oh, Merlin, is this what we get after they announced that nobody can look exactly as any other living person? So they choose the dead ones?"

"Yeah, I heard quite some witches wanted to look like some woman named Marilyn Monroe - is the original Ms. Monroe a member of the House of Monroe?"

"Mom, look at his hair. Is Salazar Slytherin's hair half black, half brown?"

"Ah, this one is entertaining, at least."

The receptionist rolled her eyes, and asked, "What is your name, sir?"

"Salazar Slytherin." The ancient lord told the truth that nobody believed.

"What is your legal name, and how long will your transfiguration last, sir?" The receptionist couldn't help but rolled her eyes again.

Salazar answered: "Well, you can temporarily call me Claudius Gamp," and he quickly added, "I would soon change the names on all the papers to Salazar Slytherin. And, a great wizard such as I can make my free transfiguration last longer than any other living wizard in the world! "

The receptionist noted down "Claudius Gamp" on the register book, and signaled for the emergency room. This surely wasn't the first self-transfigured idiot she had seen, and the transfiguration skills of those dimwits usually didn't last long.

A few minutes later, Salazar was rushed into the emergency room, and the chuckling healers there began to apply free transfiguration per Salazar's request.

"Here, my hair needs to be all black, and my skin should be fair." Salazar demanded. "Oh, and my face should be more pointed in my jaw."

In the whole while that Salazar pretended to be an idiot, Severus invisibly patched up all the imperfect transfigurations the healers didn't observe, or were too lazy to correct.

Fifteen minutes later, the head healer announced: "You are good to go, Mr., ha, Salazar Slytherin."

Salazar was then handed a portkey to Azkaban.

Severus observed that the healers didn't obtain any biological samples from Salazar, or any other patient sent to Azkaban. Since the International Regulations Against Abuse of Healing Powers was yet to pass, and this worked temporarily to Severus' advantage, Severus wasn't going to complain.

Severus knew that hair and blood would be collected by healers in Azkaban, and again by healers in Hogwarts. Severus had heard something about Muggle DNA identification technology. Moreover, even Severus knew a ton of evil things that you could do with willingly donated blood, not to mention Lord Salazar Slytherin. Therefore, both ex-Heads of Slytherin House had decided to go safe, and to only submit Claudius' samples to the people in the Hospital.

As Salazar swirled and disappeared, Severus could only hope that Salazar could really use his so-called magician's tricks to swap the samples from Salazar's own hair and blood to what they got from Claudius' body. Otherwise, well, they would have quite some busy work to do with the security system of the temporary storage room in Azkaban - if you were one of the Founders of Hogwarts, the security system in Hogwarts was relatively easy to tamper with, which Salazar had already done.

If what Severus and Salazar learned about the securities in Azkaban were right, everything on Salazar would be taken away, and he needed to change into something Muggles would recognize as restrictive clothing for the insane. Then, Salazar had to drink some sleeping potions, and would be hit several times with multiple versions of sleep and binding hexes. To counter this problem, Salazar showed Severus a Version 2.0 of the animagus transfiguration, where he could transfigure any part of his body into his animagus form. The digestive system of a basilisk could handle most potions like a breeze, and the scales of the monster snake were resistant to most hexes that were not intended to cause permanent harm. In case that the sleep hexes were to hit Salazar's head, the old lord would have to use pure magic to absorb the hexes, and made it seem like the hexes had been effective. Severus and Salazar had tried this part several times, and it proved that the all the sleep hexes the two ex-Heads of Slytherin knew could be absorbed by Salazar's magic alone. Since non wizard in Azkaban and in the Hospital was known to be much stronger than Severus - to be honest, there weren't that many in this fading age of magic in the whole world, - they were relatively safe in this regard.

Next, it would come to the question that whether Salazar's disguise would fool the diagnostic spells and artefacts used by wizards in Azkaban - they had tried the ones people used in the Room of Requirement, and the answer was yes. Severus had tried everything he knew, and everything Salazar taught him, including two spells that Severus could barely managed to cast, and the most likely result was there was nothing that couldn't be explained by "the standard idiot" statement.

Then, Salazar would be portkeyed to the Room of Requirement, checked, sampled, treated with the Stone, and sampled again.

If what Severus heard was right, anyone with malignant purposes to the Stone were to be found out at any point in Azkaban or Hogwarts, the standard protocol was to knock him or her down and arrest him immediately, and then use the Stone to fix the perpetrator in a greatly weaken state, such as a quadruple amputee without a tongue. Severus supposed that the last part was a rumor intentionally spread by Mad-Eye, for such treatment was clearly against the Boy-Who-Lived's moral standards.

Anyway, if Salazar's disguise was ever revealed, the ancient lord planned to escape with some Version 2.0 of conjured Floo fire - which the ancient lord chose not to explain it to Severus, nor had he revealed any other escape plans which he surely had. Salazar told Severus, he would then directly enter the Room of Requirement through some loophole the ancient lord would fix soon after, rob the Stone, and publicly announce his return. The only problem that Salazar saw with this alternative approach was that it might put Severus into a difficult position, while Severus had the bad feeling that the public announcement might somehow lead to a world-ending catastrophe.

Now, all Severus could do was to wait and pray in one of his secret fall-back locations in Florida. Severus dearly hoped that he wouldn't have to initiate the final back-up plan, which involved a lock of Salazar's hair, and a very special locket. Salazar claimed that he made the locket with the sacrifice of an enchanted hat, but his statement was made in English, instead of Parseltongue. Severus didn't have any immediate plan to figure out whether there was a person under the hat, for example, a certain Italian dark wizard named Giuliani. For this reason, although Salazar had said in Parseltongue that the "bad luck for offspringss" side effect was a rumor he himself made up, Severus wasn't that high on the promise the aged lord made that he would make Severus a really improved horcrux as reward.

As Severus was counting the seconds on his mechanical watch, when the watch said 6:14:05, a popping sound of a portkey announced the true return of Lord Salazar Slytherin.

Fifteen minutes later, or one hour and fourty-five minutes ago, in his suitcase-bedroom, Severus was packing his stuff for his upcoming trip for Ukraine the next morning. Somehow, he had a strange sense of true triumph, as if he had outsmarted Mad-Eye, or maybe someone or something even greater.

Author's note:

Has anyone figured out what my Horcrux Version 3.0 requires?

As I was writing this chapter, I heard the sad news that Alan Rickman, the actor who played the role of Professor Severus Snape brilliantly, had passed away. RIP, Alan. I hope someone has made a Version 3.0 Horcrux for you, so that we can still hear your unmistakable voices and watch your excellent performances after we figure out how to make a Stone.

Chapter 36: The Bicentennial House-elf

I would like to thank my beta, Kuilin.

4:43 pm, July 14th, 1993

Severus silently recounted things that he might need for his upcoming trip to Ukraine, and wondered where his sense of having forgotten something had come from. The black-haired man shook his head, and determined that it might have been caused by the many memory charms that the Boy-Who-Lived demanded for his various secrets.

-In the name of Merlin, not even Albus was this secretive!

Severus sighed, and strode toward the fireplace in his temporary residency.

As Severus was working on the security charms on the fireplace, his temporary roommate, Auror Bahry, commented from behind Severus, "Malfoy's place again?"

"And your junior female colleagues rather miss Lady Malfoy's cookies, I gather?" Severus replied sarcastically.

The Auror who had served the Department of Magical Law Enforcement for one hundred and one years gave a grunt. "Give it a break, you git! The girls hadn't been eating much of anything ever since Mad-Eye caught a hold on them."

Severus smirked, threw a pinch of Floo powder into the flames, and said, "Hogwarts Fireplace 394, one-time passcode: 022146."

As the black-haired man swirled into the Floo network, he silently admitted to himself: crazy as some of the Boy-Who-Lived's ideas might be, this suggestion of his, that every fireplace should be assigned with a random number and set with a password, is indeed quite brilliant.

When Severus stepped out from the fireplace in his old office, his godson was already waiting for him. The blond boy seemed to be under more stress than usual today.

-Draco can't be worrying about me going to the former Soviet states, can he? If that is the case, well, it is both touching and… Merlin, the new Lord Malfoy shouldn't be so soft.

"Anything you want to talk about, Draco?" Severus omitted the courtesies and asked directly.

"Yes, Godfather." Draco seemed to be a bit uneasy, "Would you apply some privacy spells?"

Severus nodded, and started to apply his common set of protection and privacy spells in the office-turned-living room, while explaining each of them in details to the blond boy. "Revelio. This is a more general form of Homenum Revelio and Specialis Revelio. Homenum Revelio, as you can guess from the incantation, only reveals human beings. It has no effect toward magical creatures, ghosts, paintings, etc. As a matter of fact, it is generally a good idea to hide a miniaturized painting of someone you trust at some places where you expect to hear some interesting conversation."

Draco's eyes moved uneasily toward where a painting of a sleeping hermit had been in this office-turned-living room. The boy had surely guessed the portrait of the same person might be hided somewhere in the Slytherin Common Room.

The ex-Head of Slytherin continued as if he hadn't noticed Draco's expressions. "Specialis Revelio detects spying charms and hexes, yet it has an unusually high failure rate at your age. Revelio, on the other hand, although it might be quite taxing for you, has a much higher success rate, and it covers more area than any sub-charm of Revelio."

Severus stopped, trying hard to remember something, and then said, "And you should practise powerful magic as much as possible. According to … something I remembered from somewhere, practising powerful magic increases your total magic level. Charms such as Protego Vitamaxima would do. Oh, and you can try to learn some Muggle magicians' tricks, those might help with wand movements."

Severus swayed a bit as he said the last sentence, and he had no idea where the "magicians' tricks" part came from.

The blond boy looked at Severus, a bit worried, "Godfather, are you alright?"

Severus nodded, wanted to curse Mad-Eye, but checked his tongue in front of his possibly-too-soft godson. "I really need to be harsher on Mad-Eye when it is my turn to memory charm him. Now try Revelio."

As Severus corrected Draco's wand movements, he pondered Draco's previous question: thanks to Mad-Eye and the Boy-Who-Lived, I have so many mental lapses! In my current mental state, it would be dangerous for me to wander into unfamiliar territories. However, why do I have a false sense of security? Where does it come from? What the hell has Mad-Eye or the Boy-Who-Lived done to me? Did they do something similar to Draco as well?

About half an hour later, Severus finished his last privacy spell, and allowed the sweaty and tired blond boy to sit down.

Severus reached into his pouch, drew out a golden locket, and tossed it to Draco. "If you open the locket, and press the button inside, then for the next fifteen minutes, within a radius of about two meters, it would be equivalent to around two thirds of the sequence of spells I just showed you. It can only be used about ten times. Don't rely too much on it."

"Godfather, thank you so much." Draco examined the locket admiringly, "Godfather, did you make it yourself?"

Severus raised one eyebrow and smirked smugly - if there were some leisure time, he wouldn't mind going into details on how difficult it was to combine and store eighteen powerful charms into one locket, and how there were only a limited number of wizards in the world who could do it. However, there might be more pressing matters. "Draco, what was the matter that you wanted to discuss?"

Draco put the locket into his pouch, looked a bit uneasy, and said, "Godfather, I had wondered if you might need a house-elf."

Severus raised one eyebrow, and suggested: "I gather, the Boy-Who-Lived's comments on this subject changed your view?"

Severus clearly remembered the Potter boy's weird questions toward Draco and him concerning house-elves.

The Boy-Who-Lived had asked about whether the house-elves would hurt other wizards or themselves upon commands from their masters. The answer was obviously yes and yes. While Severus gave several examples where house-elves were used as killers, and Draco supplemented with information on how the old families usually blocked house-elves of other families from coming in, Harry Potter frowned in a way that strikingly resembled Albus Dumbledore.

Then, Harry Potter asked how the house-elves processed commands given by various beings. Draco answered that house-elves would obey their masters' orders first, then other family members', other peoples' when they were the masters' guests, for courtesy reasons. They didn't give a dime about what other non-human creatures requested them to do - though he admitted that house-elves might take orders from the paintings of deceased masters.

Harry Potter pondered on this, and asked a really odd question: "Do the house-elves always know themselves as house-elves, and define themselves as house-elves?"

Severus remembered that he and Draco had exchanged some worried glances, and Draco had hesitantly answered, "I suppose, yes? Dobby used to say, 'Dobby is such a bad elf', or something like that."

Then, there came the really worrying question: "Can the house-elves be ordered to harm human beings as a whole?"

Severus had responded, "Mr. Potter, I wonder if the house-elves are capable of understanding complex concepts such as 'human beings as a whole'. If the house-elves can foresee their actions might hurt their masters, they would not do so, however, their masters can explicitly demand them to. I have heard that a certain house-elf was forced by its master to assist in her suicide. The poor house-elf became mad and attempted to kill itself several times before our respectable Aurors could put it into Azkaban. Therefore, if someone commands his or her house-elf to conduct some act that might bring an end to this world, it probably would obey."

Finally, after discussing in secrecy with Granger again, the Boy-Who-Lived asked Severus if he could try to figure out how to make house-elves, and especially, how to alter the predetermined rules that these conjured creatures would follow.

During the past week, besides practising his bribery skills with the help of Lucius on officials in the German Ministry of Magic, and doing something that Severus couldn't remember now, he had spent almost all his spare time on this question.

-Too bad that I can't even share my progresses with my godson or Lucius.

The proud black-haired wizard regrettably thought.

Severus eyed his godson who was looking at him with worry and concern, and smiled reassuringly, "Draco, you don't need to give me a house-elf. Maybe, I would be able to conjure some for you later."

"Godfather, I know that we shouldn't rely too much on house-elves, but it is always good to have more security measures, isn't it?" Draco said, "If you would like to, I can temporarily transfer the ownership of any Malfoy elf - besides Dobby - to you."

Severus smelt something odd in Draco's words, and asked: "What about Dobby? Isn't it the house-elf that your Father used to bring everywhere? - If this concerns some privacy issues, you don't need to answer."

Draco's lips twisted, and his eyebrows frowned. "After Harry asked those weird questions, I observed the Malfoy elves more closely. And I found that all the elves were happy beyond themselves upon Father's return, except Dobby. It seemed that Dobby wasn't happy at all. I knew Father wasn't generally nice toward house-elves, but he wasn't deliberately cruel, either. Dobby, Dobby might be a special case for Father. Dobby was actually assigned as my personal elf when I was born. After Mother was taken away, Father might have blamed every cough I had on Dobby, and, err, punished Dobby accordingly. Father might think taking Dobby everywhere was a good training program for Dobby, so it would later serve me better. After I observed that Dobby was behaving oddly upon Father's return, I demanded a true answer from it. Besides almost knocking itself into concussions, it said that 'Old master is bad person', and 'Dobby is to running to the Boy-Who-Lived, and warn him of the return of the bad wizard, if the bad master didn't turn himself in'. In the name of Merlin, this kind of treason shouldn't even be possible for house-elves!"

"What? Where is Dobby now?" Severus almost rose from his chair. "Have you demanded true answers concerning loyalty to your family from other elves?"

Draco answered: "I have subdued Dobby, tied it up with multiple methods, and it is currently being watched by other elves in the Manor. As for the other elves, they are all cleared of everything."

Severus nodded, "Bring it to me. I need to check it for various mind controlling magic. Hopefully, this is the cause… Oh, don't look at me like that, Draco. If a house-elf is genuinely capable of treason, the wizarding kind is in much greater trouble than a single house-elf being controlled."

Draco's face turned white.

Twenty minutes of busy wand works later, Severus admitted that he didn't find any signs of mind controlling magic on Dobby, and Legilimens seemed to suggest that this little creature genuinely resented Lucius, and it also desired the gravest punishment for house-elves: freedom.

-Damn it!

Severus took in a deep breath, and said to his godson: "Draco, I think we need to notify Potter - and bloody Mad-Eye - that this kind of thing is even possible. We need to check every single house-elf in this castle!"

Five minutes later, when Severus began to explain how Dobby might be capable of treason to Harry Potter, Hermione Granger, and Mad-Eye, the Girl-Who-Revived seemed to have taken much delight upon the news that house-elves might want freedom. The girl radiating purity and innocence was looking at the new Lord Malfoy expectantly, as if it was a sin not to give Dobby his freedom.

Severus knew he shouldn't let his godson appear to be the bad guy in front of the Boy-Who-Lived and the Girl-Who-Revived, so he himself snapped, "Miss Granger, the majority of house-elves in Hogwarts are probably descendants of those conjured by Lord Salazar Slytherin! If the house-elves are capable of betraying their supposed mistress Headmistress Minerva McGonagall, why wouldn't they decide to rid Muggleborns from the school? Or, enlighten me, why can't a free-spirited house-elf just decide that it wants to steal the Stone from Hogwarts?"

Although Mad-Eye pretended that he was busy casting spells on Dobby to avoid commenting on this issue, Severus knew the paranoid old Auror agreed with him on this point.

While the girl with amazing grace, speed, and physical strength stared angrily at Severus, and Severus stared back without a blink, the Boy-Who-Lived murmured, "The Bicentennial Man, no, The Bicentennial House-elf."

Severus looked at Harry Potter in bewilderment, "Mr. Potter, the house-elves do have a life expectancy of two hundred years, but Dobby is quite young for an elf. Does this has something to do with the age of elves?"

Harry Potter shook his head, then hesitated, and sighed, "Yes, we should check all the house-elves in Hogwarts for any original thoughts. And, err, Draco, AFTER we make sure that it is safe, could you give Dobby its freedom?"

Before Draco could respond, Harry yelled with panic: "Oh, wait, forget my last sentence for now!"

The Girl-Who-Revived immediately directed her stares toward the Boy-Who-Lived.

"Hermione, I can't say it! I really can't say it!"

This proclamation sent chills down everyone's spine.

Chapter 37: Nurmengard Pt I, German Minister of Magic

I would like to thank my beta, Kuilin. After Kuilin's diligent work, I suppose I can update this story twice per week for a while.

9:46 am, July 15th, 1993

Ever since 1952, the West German Ministry of Magic put into place a rather peculiar tradition: that all appointees to the position of guard at the Nurmengard Wizarding Prison needed to be interviewed and approved by the Minister of Magic. It was not that the men and women on the top of the political structure had no better things to occupy their time with, nor did it mean the Ministers were all power-hungry busybodies who couldn't handle any power - no matter how small - to their subordinates. It was because of a single name: Gellert Grindelwald.

If the matter were given to the hands of Rudolf Schmidt, the current German Minister of Magic, sometimes he just wished the winners of World War II just decided to handle Grindelwald to the dementors, instead of creating a permanent problem for the Ministry of Magic.

Unfortunately, after Albus Dumbledore defeated Gellert Grindelwald, both the Russians and the Americans wanted to get the secrets Lord Grindelwald knew, especially why he had been invincible as a result of the Muggles he sacrificed. And the Brits, since they got the majority of Grindelwald's ancient relic collections, and maybe since Albus Dumbledore had a special soft spot for the blond dark lord, did not protest the decision to keep the lives of the cold blooded murderers and warmongers of the previous Wizarding World War.

From a certain point of view, Rudolf Schmidt could understand why the lords and ladies who wielded real power wanted to keep Grindelwald alive; but what he didn't understand was why the Americans, the Russians, and the French had regular visits with Grindelwald, and swindled Merlin knew how many secrets out of him, while the Germans had to be held responsible for the safety of Nurmengard!

-Don't they know that all German wizards and witches with real powers are either dead, or in Nurmengard? And no security is perfect unless it has some powerful wizards or witches behind it!

Rudolf had suspected that, if it were only up to the lords and ladies in Washington, D.C., or up to the comrades in Moscow, they might decide to torture the secrets out of Grindelwald, hence ending the permanent problem. However, Washington and Moscow were obviously not friends, and they fought fervently for moral high grounds on such eyeball-attracting matters.

-And not to mention the goodie-oldie Albus Dumbledore, who was against torture of any kind!

To be fair, before June 1992, the only thing that kept the previous West German Ministers of Magic asleep at night was the fact that Albus Dumbledore, the most powerful wizard in the world, paid Grindelwald a monthly visit, and checked the securities of Nurmengard. The fact that Grindelwald promised Dumbledore that he would not escape might have helped, but nobody wanted to rely too much on that promise, nobody except the goodie-oldie Albus Dumbledore, anyway.

Unfortunately, even Albus Dumbledore couldn't stop Grindelwald from parceling some of his dark secrets to unwanted ears. In 1947, there was a prisoner named Emeric Meyer, who was sentenced four years into the prison for multiple petty thefts. This man was assigned to Grindelwald as his errand boy. According to what Rudolf heard, it was because you didn't want the most dangerous dark lord in the European Continent to decide that he wanted to run away for trivial things such as the taste of his morning coffee, or the way his bed was made, and because Emeric Meyer was weak in magic and was pretty slow in the brain department - according to his interrogators, anyway. Rudolf had doubted whether the Americans might be behind this decision as well. Not entirely a surprise for anyone, only one year after Emeric Meyer was released, that man became a very dangerous dark wizard. It took three really powerful wizards to track him down and kill him. Rudolf had suspected that if those three were not each from the United States, France, and the Soviet Union, it might not take that many powerful wizards to do it, nor might Meyer be killed during his arrest.

It was needless to say that the world powers had put more efforts into persuading Lord Grindelwald into parceling out more of his secrets ever since, and no prisoners with any sentence shorter than lifetime imprisonment was allowed anywhere near Grindelwald.

Unfortunately, the Ministry couldn't restrict the freedom of the prison guards after their job. The Ministry had wanted to let every guard take an Unbreakable Vow of some sort, yet both the Americans and the Russians had fervently objected any idea of that sort for "human rights reasons". Rudolf was sure that some of the guards were actually American spies, or Russian spies, or both, and Grindelwald might know who was on which side better than the poor West German Ministry of Magic.

-Well, while American Muggle troops and wizarding delegations were in one part of your country, and the Russians were in the other part, one couldn't actually argue the unfairness of the whole matter. At least, when the Americans had five to seven powerful lords and ladies, and the Russians had three to five comrades, magical West Germany, which had none, had no bargaining power whatsoever.

In the 1970s, while the extraordinary powerful dark wizard who named himself Lord Voldemort rose into power in Great Britain, many people had suspected that this man had somehow gained magical knowledge from Grindelwald. Lord Grindelwald had neither confirmed nor denied that speculation.

After David Monroe was supposedly killed by Lord Voldemort, Bartemius Crouch, the Director of the Department of Law Enforcement in the British Ministry of Magic had called the international wizarding society for help. The Americans, the Russians and the French had offered nothing more or less than their utmost moral support.

Some presumptuous Muggle-loving nerds had explained the reluctance of the international community to offer any real help to the Brits as some laughable Muggle psychology terms, such as "bystander effect". However, Rudolf had a much better explanation: the Brits had possessed too many powerful magical relics and secrets for too long.

On the Muggle side of the world, if the Americans and Russians had cooperated in one really important matter since the end of World War II, it was the demolition of the British and French colonial system. After World War II, both the Muggle British and Muggle French government had tried both diplomatic and military approaches to continue their reigns in their colonies, yet the Americans and the Russians had sabotaged all their efforts. In the Suez Crisis, while Muggle Britain and France allied with Israel and started a military operation in Suez Canal to keep their special interest in Egypt, the Americans staged a run on the pounds while the Russians threatened Britain and France with a nuclear war. With the efforts from the Americans and Russians, the 1960s and 1970s witnessed the birth of many newly independent states, and Great Britain was no longer an imperial power.

On the wizarding side of things, however, Great Britain had Albus Dumbledore, the most powerful wizard in the world. Since the old man was never interested in helping the Muggles of his country maintain their colonial system, the goodie-oldie was highly praised by both the Free and the Communist countries, and was showered with all kinds of honors. However, by the 1970s, when most of the British colonies had declared independence, and the Americans and the Russians each got their share of the game, the most powerful wizard in the world began to seem too old and too stubborn with his important secrets.

Therefore, while Lord Voldemort rose out of nowhere - some speculated Grindelwald was behind him, others suspected the Americans or Russians were backing him up, while some even speculated whether the hands of the Chinese or Japanese were involved - the world just held back their hands and observed what Albus Dumbledore could do.

To the amazement of the entire wizarding world, each time Lord Voldemort seemed to have gained the upper hand, Albus Dumbledore could pull something out of his magical hat, or did something really complicated and weird, and then he was able to regain some advantage. And in 1981, Lord Voldemort was vanquished - surely by a trap from Dumbledore, not some baby - and Dumbledore had proved that he was the better man.

The world became much friendlier toward Dumbledore after that, and the interest in Grindelwald's secrets reached a new height - everyone who wielded real power knew that Dumbledore and Grindelwald were close in their youth, and it was against common sense to think that these two gained their ancient knowledge through different means.

The demolition of the Berlin Wall and the end of the Cold War brought a major reorganization to the Ministry of Magic, and Rudolph became the first German - no longer West German, or East German, just German - Minister of Magic.

Unfortunately, the reunification of the two German Ministries of Magic hadn't ended the permanent problem in Nurmengard - Rudolf had hoped the Americans had decided to just take Grindelwald to Washington as a trophy for winning the Cold War, but the goodie-oldie Albus Dumbledore was still the most powerful wizard in the world, so the Americans didn't even try.

One year ago, the day when Lord Voldemort suddenly reappeared and was subsequently vanquished again, the Flamels were slaughtered, and Albus Dumbledore disappeared as well. The story the Boy-Who-Lived recounted was obviously a lie for anyone with a shred of a brain - many had agreed that the Flamels might be killed by Voldemort, while Voldemort might be defeated by the combined forces of Albus Dumbledore and the previously disappeared David Monroe.

Before anyone had figured out what really happened that night, or, more importantly, what actually happened to Albus Dumbledore, the British wizards shocked the rest of the world again, by offering the healing power of the Philosopher's Stone to everyone in the world. This overtly nice gesture and the attribution of all glories to a young child had some resemblance to the wired plots of the goodie-oldie, but it was too good to be true even for Albus Dumbledore.

And after Gellert Grindelwald learned that Albus Dumbledore was "frozen in Time", and the Philosopher's Stone was available to anyone with lethal conditions, he claimed that he might be able to unravel some mysteries related to "the origin of magic" if he were given the chance to try to rescue Dumbledore from Time and study the Stone. Lord Grindelwald even promised that he would take Unbreakable Vows of any contents that might satisfy the British, German, and American magical authorities before doing so.

Grindelwald's eagerness forced all the lords and ladies with real power and intelligence to pause and think before they made any efforts in robbing or stealing the Stone.

Though Rudolf himself was never powerful enough to anywhere near the level of Albus Dumbledore - otherwise, nobody would make him Minister of Magic - sometimes, he couldn't help but to wonder if Albus Dumbledore had plotted the whole thing.

-Maybe the old man finally realized his old age, and foresaw what might happen to Great Britain once he died. Perhaps he had sacrificed his own life and magic, - or maybe that of the unfortunate Flamels, Monroe, Lord Voldemort, and Death Eaters - to construct some formidable protections against all potential enemies.

-Maybe the Stone is just a bizarre lure, and something unspeakable would happen to anyone who made a real effort to get it. This thing may only be able to strike a limited number of times, but nobody wants to be the first one at the receiving end of Dumbledore's final weird plot.

-Moreover, who can be sure that Albus Dumbledore is actually "disappeared"? Great Britain had witnessed the disappearances and reappearances of Lord Voldemort, David Monroe, the Girl-Who-Revived, and most recently, Lucius Malfoy. Who can say that Dumbledore isn't going to be the next one?

-Maybe this is indeed something related to the origin of magic, as Grindelwald had claimed. In that case, the whole affair might relate to why Dumbledore and Grindelwald had risen to their level of power. Then...

Not being a really powerful wizard himself, Rudolf couldn't quite fathom the "what-ifs" in case the matter involved the origin of magic, but he knew it was enough to cause the world's lords and ladies to temporarily halt their plans.

-Maybe they want Grindelwald to test things out first, or maybe something else.

It was needless to say that Madam Bones' insistence that all prisoners in Azkaban should be moved to Nurmengard attracted more attention to a particular prisoner, and the whole world wondered the real reason behind this bizarre act.

-True, the dementor treatment before was highly inhuman, but after the Girl-Who-Revived supposedly killed all dementors, why did they still have to move every prisoner to Nurmengard? Actually, why did they get rid of all dementors in the first place? They suddenly became better persons? What a joke!

Under the pressure from the curious Americans, Rudolf agreed to accept the British prisoners. Luckily for him, most of the prisoners had gone mad due to years of exposure to dementors, and they could be easily managed. And, since then, the British Ministry of Magic had only handed him common criminals, and nobody needed to be locked into the lifetime wards in which Grindelwald was held.

After a year, poor Rudolf had fantasized that things might have settled down a bit, yet he knew that was too good to be true: the aged Lord Gellert Grindelwald was on the waiting list for the use of the Stone, and it would be his turn to return to youth in two months. After that, Rudolf wondered what forces could possibly hold the rejuvenated most powerful wizard in the world in the very prison that he built.

For what was worse, three weeks ago, the supposedly dead Lucius Malfoy suddenly reappeared. From the looks of it, the British Ministry of Magic had every intention to put this intelligent ex-Death Eater into the lifetime wards.

-For Merlin's sake, who are they kidding? The very Death Eater whose son is a very close friend to the Boy-Who-Lived, and who had been an ally of Harry Potter? And you are telling me the Brits are not up to something?

-Is it a plot on the Brits' part to get in contact with Grindelwald? Or are they trying to warn the rest of the world that Dumbledore might return anytime?

-Who would reappear next? Charles Nott, whose son is closed to Potter as well? Any other Death Eaters? Any previous holders of Line of Merlin Unbroken? Hogwarts Four? Merlin himself? I wonder when the Brits get this habit of reappearing after their supposed death!

-Moreover, damn the Americans! I am quite sure they are going to pressure me to put Malfoy together with Grindelwald, just to see what happens next!

And now, after what appeared that Lord Voldemort might have made another return, Rudolf was faced again with the permanent devil for every German Minister of Magic: approving a prison guard for the lifetime wards of Nurmengard.

During the years, Rudolf had already given up the hope of figuring out why each and everyone of those intelligent people applied for the low-paying and low-status jobs in Nurmengard; if the power behind the applicants were the from Americans, Russians, French, or whoever; and whether they were just some self-motivated wannabe dark wizards.

At any rate, Rudolf Schmidt glanced again at the resume of the best candidate for this job, a likeable young chap named Alexander Dimitrov. According to the papers, his parents were heros in the war against Grindelwald, he was educated in Durmstrang, graduated with outstanding marks, and had several suspicious "international traveling" years after graduation. In a word, he was the common sort of people who applied for prison guard jobs in Nurmengard.

-Damn the Americans! Ever since the end of the Cold War, they have even abandoned the courtesy to make the resumes look at least inconspicuous!

Rudolf sighed, and signaled his secretary to let Alexander Dimitrov in.

Chapter 38: Nurmengard Pt II, Lucius Malfoy

I would like to thank my beta, Kuilin. After Kuilin's diligent work, I suppose I can update this story twice per week for a while.

10:23 am, July 15th, 1993

According to the rushed decision by the survivors of the eighty-ninth Wizengamot, Lucius Abraxas Malfoy, aka. Mr. White, was sentenced 357 years in prison for his previous crimes as a Death Eater. Since the ex-Lord Malfoy, who was now only Mr. Malfoy, had been quite cooperative in his trials, and he had some unspecified "considerable contributions to the wizarding society and the world", the prison sentence had been reduced to 234 years. Lucius hoped that his wisdom and luck would help him to significantly shorten this unpleasant period of time, though that highly depends on how he would perform in the next two months.

Handcuffed behind his back, baggy orange prison robes on his body, the ex-Lord Malfoy was escorted through the yard of Nurmengard towards the lifetime wards by three prison guards. Trying to ignore the grim future prospect that this might be his residence for a long time, the blond man observed the jet black castle.

The sounds of huge waves clashing with rocks and the damp and salty wind told everyone inside Nurmengard that the prison was located on a rocky cliff near the North Sea, From what Lucius read before he came here, viewing from outside, the black formidable fortress was rectangular in shape, with four towering keeps in each corner. A glimpse from inside told Lucius that the prison guards on the towers could effectively shoot every inch of the rectangular inner yard, leaving no blind spot. According to the newspapers, during the past year, the northeast corner of the castle had been transformed into the "Healing and Consultation Center", and it was where most of the dementor-exposed former prisoners of Azkaban were located. From what Lucius had heard, the healings didn't make much progress. Heading to southwest, Lucius supposed that the rumors that the lifetime wards were located in the southwest corner might be true. However, for a magical castle that might or might not have some resemblance to Hogwarts or Azkaban in its defensive wards, judging the orientations according to the sun could be misleading, and the direction of the gates bore no indications of the actual directions while you were inside the castle.

After the two guards in front of the southwest corner gate and the guards escorting Lucius exchanged some passwords, Lucius and the guards were lead through a Thief's Downfall, and were probed with a series of interesting magical devices. About five minutes later, the southwest corner gate creaked open, and the blond prisoner became the subject of another round of checks after he went through the gate. Finally, the new prisoner and guard trio were allowed to step into the corridors.

Although the outside of Nurmengard was a standard high-security magical castle, amazingly, the inside resembled -

With a suppressed shudder, Lucius remembered the pictures of Muggle concentration camps that he recently saw: the walls were deathly white, the floor was gloomy grey, and the corridors were depressingly straight and narrow, with tall black iron prison cell doors meticulously arranged on each side.

-Did he, did he want to sacrifice his wizarding prisoners the same way he used the Muggles to be invincible?

When it was all about how Grindelwald killed millions of Muggles to gain infinite power, Lucius never thought much of it - the world might be a better place with more of those pests gone; and if Grindelwald had done it sooner, the "nuclear weapons" that had worried Severus so much probably wouldn't even exist. However, to consider the possibility that the Malfoys might one day lose his Lordship's favor in the hypothetic scenario that Grindelwald had won, and this might be the place where the Malfoys might end up with…

Swallowing down hard, Lucius admitted to himself that Albus Dumbledore might have done one good thing in his life.

Several long corridors and five stairs up later, where Lucius figured that the castle was much larger from the inside than from outside, the guard trio stopped in front of Zelle 537, and opened the heavy iron door. Lucius stepped into the cell, and the door closed behind him immediately. Then, the guards opened a small opening in the larger door, and instructed Lucius to put his hands through the small door. While one of the guards was untying the handcuffs, Lucius eyed the small single cell - unfortunately, his single cell.

This room was approximately half of the size of the semi-comfortable holding cell in the Department of Magical Law Enforcement, yet it was much better than the abysmal conditions for prisoners of Azkaban before it was turned into the Hospital - not that the prisoners would notice anything with the presence of dementors. Although any common sense of orientation would determine it as impossible, Lucius could still see the gloomy North Sea through the small window. Lucius suppose, this view was better than the grim sight of the Nurmengard inner yard - the Boy-Who-Lived probably didn't lie about that the ex-Lord Malfoy would get the best reasonable treatment in Nurmengard. Beside the window, there was a neatly-made single bed with grey sheet, and all the corners of the bed was round, and perhaps magically cushioned. Near the head of the bed stood a small round-cornered hardwood desk, and a chair affixed to some rails on the concrete floor, so that you could only move it forward or backward in front of the desk, yet there was no way that you could lift the chair up and use it as a weapon. Near the end of the bed, there was a small chest drawer. If the German prison officials were not boasting about their working efficiency, the limited underclothes and other items that Lucius was allowed to bring here should already be inside it. Besides the chest drawer, there was the toilet and the standing shower. As Impervius charms eliminated the practical necessity of walls and curtains between the shower and other furnitures, and the privacy of prisoners were not of much concern to the designers of this fortress, Lucius supposed that he had to swallow down this unpleasant adjustment to his lifestyle.

As his hands were free from the handcuffs, and the small door in the clunky iron door was shut behind, Lucius rubbed his wrists, and moved toward the small wooden desk. Lucius opened the drawer in the desk, and found the real luxury that he was allowed to purchase in Nurmengard: newspapers.

Lucius flipped through the headlines in the Daily Prophet, and found no new instructions from the Boy-Who-Lived, - well, he just finished the conversation with the Potter boy merely ten hours ago, so there was no need for new instructions on today's newspaper.

Lucius frowned as he thought of the uncomfortable conversation yesterday, where the Boy-Who-Lived grilled him about everything he did to the treacherous little creature named Dobby. Under the angry stares from the Girl-Who-Revived and sneers from Mad-Eye, Lucius admitted that he had used some illegal-on-human magic on Dobby. To avoid further judgements from the Granger girl and Mad-Eye, Lucius changed into Parseltongue to list the various curses he had employed, such as Cruciatus Curse, Imperius Curse, Gom jabbar, and something else along the same line.

Unfortunately, the Boy-Who-Lived had to ask Severus and Mad-Eye about the effects and rumors on each curse in detail in English, and Lucius had to endure the Girl-Who-Revived's constant judgements.

"Err, the Cruciatus Curse breaks one's soul? I mean, could you explain it in less metaphoric words?" The Potter boy had asked.

Lucius was first confused by Potter's question, because "breaks one's soul" was exactly what Cruciatus Curse did, there was nothing metaphoric about it, and the potion that could mitigate the sufferings of Cruciatus victims was called "Soul Healing Potion".

From later discussion between Severus and Potter, Lucius realized that the Boy-Who-Lived didn't believe in the existence of souls.

-But that is ridiculous! If wizards don't have souls, how can animagus think? How does Polyjuice work?

Lucius wanted to utter his disagreement, yet he checked his tongue, because he didn't want to contradict his new Light Lord on such theoretical issues.

Then, something hit Lucius: I don't remember anything happening between the point of my death and the point of my revival! Therefore, therefore...

Lucius drew in a horrified breath: there is no afterlife.

Mad-Eye observed Lucius' change in breath, and snarled, "What, Lucius? You'd better spell it out, for your own sake!"

Lucius sighed, "Lord Potter, I have just realized that I can attest to your idea that there is no afterlife. At least, there is nothing that I can recall between my death and revival. I sspoke truth."

"OK, then we can eliminate the whole 'creation-of-a-soul' thing from our discussion." The Potter boy proclaimed. "Let's move to the breach of predetermined magical rules."

To Lucius' slight amazement, Severus chose to refute the new Light Lord's idea: "Mr. Potter, you do realize that soul and afterlife are two different concepts. As an animagus and a potioneer, I still tend to believe in the existence of souls. There are potions that claim to be able to heal or damage souls, and it appears that the potions perform their functions as described."

While Severus and Potter entered a rather academic discussion, Lucius re-evaluated his new Light Lord.

-The Boy-Who-Lived doesn't seem to be bothered by such disagreements. Well, this is something different from Riddle.

Just then, the Girl-Who-Revived raised her head from a bulky book that she was reading, and asked, "In the description in this book, Gom jabbar and a poisonous needle can be used to test if someone is a human or an animal, for a human can endure the pain caused by Gom jabbar, and not to flinch toward the poisonous needle, while an animal cannot. So how did Dobby react to your Gom jabbar, and what did you say or do around the time you punish Dobby with Gom jabbar?"

Lucius tried hard to remember, and answered, "I told it not to scream, otherwise I would punish it more severely. And after a few times, Dobby stopped screaming during my punishments. But how can that make it a human?"

"Oh, Lucius, oh, Lucius, you dimwit! " Severus - instead of anyone else - snapped at him."You set a test and asked Dobby to behave like a human, or to be a human! The master's orders are the highest laws of house-elves, so Dobby did!"

Lucius wanted to protest, and yet he found Severus' arguments quite convincing.

The girl radiating a sense of innocence and purity said in amazement: "So the cruel master is the reason that Dobby is capable of a mind of its own!"

"A mind of its own?" The Boy-Who-Lived repeated the Girl-Who-Revived's words with his eyes wide open.

Lucius had a sense that the Potter boy had just discovered something very important. And judging from the change of expression on Severus' face, Lucius guessed his new best friend had thought of something really important as well.

As for what they might have figured out, Lucius hadn't figured out yet. Lucius supposed, if he was unlucky, he would have hundreds of years to decrypt this mystery.

Comparing to some rather theoretical magic problems, Lucius would rather prefer to entangle some political conundrum, such as why the world's top wizards hadn't attacked Hogwarts yet. After Lucius instructed Severus to bribe the right bureaucrats, and asked the right questions, it turned out that they owed quite a lot to Albus Dumbledore's reputation of weirdness and power, and Grindelwald's reaction to the events one year ago. Lucius wondered if Lord Grindelwald had considered Great Britain as his own playground after Dumbledore was locked in Time, and said something specifically designed to deter the Americans and Russians from doing anything real.

Unfortunately for Lucius, even in the field that he considered his game, the major players might consider magic theory more important than politics, for Lord Grindelwald had claimed that the reason Albus Dumbledore disappeared had something to do with the "origin of magic", and this, somehow made the rest of the world pause and think.

After Severus delivered Grindelwald's statement to the Boy-Who-Lived the day before yesterday, Severus, Draco, the Granger girl, and the Potter boy all agreed the claim itself might be true; while Mad-Eye, who had been approached by people who tried to deliver the same statement from Lord Grindelwald before, didn't believe a single word.

Lucius had never walked the walks of powerful wizards, and he had never dreamt that he would - what Lucius excelled at was people. By comparing the different reactions of Potter, Granger, Severus, and Mad-Eye upon the previous "origin of magic" issue and the house-elf issue, Lucius could sort of fancy why Mad-Eye failed in his attempt to become a really powerful lord: this guy is slower in powerful wizardry than I am.

For the next thirty minutes or so, Lucius watched as they discussed "free will", "predetermined magical rules" and "origin of magic", where Severus and Potter did most of the talking. Lucius didn't quite understand all the contents they were talking about, but he could see one thing: if anyone in the Potter boy's headquarter office is going to be a really powerful lord, Potter and Severus have the best chances.

Lucius started to consider how he should treat Severus differently after this discovery, and contemplated what this might mean for his future plans.

-The Boy-Who-Lived, the Girl-Who-Revived, Severus, and Grindelwald, are all more interested in powerful wizardry than current politics. Maybe I should instruct Draco to do the same, and stick closer to his new Godfather.

-Thinking along the same line, I should change my approach when I meet Grindelwald. The leverages that I can use on Lord Grindelwald should be important secrets on powerful wizardry. The problem with this approach is that I can hardly see the danger in any of the important secrets I know, maybe Severus and Potter might enlighten me on this.

When Severus and Potter reached the point that they were full of speculations and without enough power or resources to confirm or falsify the majority of the ideas, Lucius raised his point, and asked what he could offer Lord Grindelwald.

Then, Severus and Potter entered another long academic discussion, while Mad-Eye were either suggesting that Lucius raised this question because he was up to something, or pointing out how dangerous each secret could be.

-This old lunatic is good at one thing: how dangerous everything could be.

Finally, they agreed on one least harmful secret: part of the reason Hermione Granger was like this, had something to do with the sacrifice of an unicorn (as many had already guessed out); and in case something happened to the Girl-Who-Revived, there would be so much backlashes from the Universe, that the origin of magic might be destroyed (many people already knew the rumor about unicorn blood and Liquid Luck, anyway).

Therefore, now Lucius was stuck with only one thing that he could offer Lord Grindelwald (which Lord Grindelwald might already know), and his task was to wiggle out what the Russians and Americans had been trying for the past fifty years from the clearly very intelligent Lord Grindelwald.

Lucius sighed, and continued to imagine various scenarios how his first meeting with Lord Grindelwald would go.

Chapter 39: Nurmengard Pt III, Gellert Grindelwald

I would like to thank my beta, Kuilin. After Kuilin's diligent work, I suppose I can update this story twice per week for a while.

9:24 am, July 16th, 1993

Lord Gellert Grindelwald sat by his large oak desk in his luxurious study, and flipped through the preprints of the next month's The Practical Potioneer - after being the one of the world's top magical researchers in secret for almost fifty years, this was what you got as a privilege: access to anything published or to be published.

However, Lord Grindelwald's heart wasn't on the improvements of Soul Healing Potion highlighted in the magazine at all, he was pondering on what the Brits wanted to deliver to him by sending Lucius Malfoy here.

Lord Grindelwald wasn't lying when he said that the reason Albus Dumbledore was locked in Time could be related to the origin of magic. With the blatantly obvious traps dear old Albus set up the year before, which couldn't even stop a first year Hogwarts students from entering, there had been enough foolish and defenseless students entering the chamber where there was a large golden mirror that they could see what they desire on the mirror. Various sources - ranging from the Americans, Russians, to self-aspired dark wizards - had all confirmed the existence of such a mirror. From the description, Grindelwald could only think of one mirror: the Mirror of Noitilov.

Grindelwald had never seen the Mirror, but he had heard and read enough of it: the Mirror of Perfect Reflection, older than Merlin himself, where phoenixes came from, probably a relic from the Atlantis, where it all began.

-The Mirror of Noitilov and the Stone of Permanency, what a typical British trap! So full of ancient relics and mysteries, and so powerful. Just the type of thing my dear old Albus prefers.

-Maybe it is due to the influence of Albus, the Brits are such a hopeless lot! When the rest of the world has moved forward, they are still clinging hard on old glories. During all his monthly visits, Albus didn't even ask me what I have accomplished. He just simply ruled everything as "too cruel to hear about". What a ridiculous lunatic!

Resentments toward old Albus aside, Grindelwald did think the Mirror and the Stone had everything to do with the origin of magic, and he was indeed quite interested in studying them. Although dear old Albus probably had set up some sort of trap there - maybe specifically for him, Grindelwald didn't plan to give up on entangling the biggest mystery in history without even trying.

-If what the Brits said had a single shred of truth in it, the reason Albus disappeared indeed has something to do with Time, - a character both the Mirror of Noitilov and the Stone of Permanency share, Albus got to have invoked some arcane power in those relics. What other things could be "locked in Time"? Secrets of Atlantis? Creators of the Mirror and the Stone?

-Literally for the sake of Atlantis, I would very much like to rescue the creators of the Mirror and the Stone from Time. Albus, sorry, you are just such a small bonus as comparing to them.

A year's time had already allowed Grindelwald to formulate hundreds of plans that he could try on the Mirror and the Stone, yet everything was in vain unless he could actually lay his hands on these ancient relics.

It was not that Lord Grindelwald, currently the most powerful wizard in the world, couldn't escape from the very prison he himself designed that had prevented him from escaping, it was the combined effects of the lack of the Death Stick, the lack of the sacrificing Muggles, and his fading age, that had made Lord Grindelwald unsure of the prospect of facing down the combined forces of half a dozen wizarding lords and ladies. If everything could be managed, Grindelwald would rather prefer to regain his youth first, and to study the origin of magic peacefully (and without the possibly dreadful Unbreakable Vow) later. As for conquering the world, and ruling the Muggles, those could all wait until Lord Grindelwald figured out literally the most important secret in history.

Hence, Grindelwald was quite interested in what Lucius Malfoy was about to deliver.

A beeping sound notified Grindelwald the arrival of his visitor.

Grindelwald strode toward his living room, glanced through the view mirror, and saw the blond new prisoner and the guard trio who were escorting the British aristocrat. Among the guards, was one chubby-faced brown-haired newbie, possibly Alexander Dimitrov.

-Ah, the new boys, always so eager.

Grindelwald checked his protection wards, and pressed a button. It was something ironic that you even needed to be careful when you were locked up in the very prison you designed. In the early days of his imprisonment, Grindelwald went through at least four assassination attempts by both some prison guards and follow inmates, before the Americans and the Russians agreed that Lord Grindelwald's mind was way too precious to be destroyed by some amateur hero-wannabe or avenge-seeker, thus they gradually increased the range of magic that the former dark lord was legally allowed to use.

As the iron door slowly opened, Grindelwald appraised the messenger from United Kingdom. This ex-Lord Malfoy was a fine specimen of a poster Aryan wizard: pureblood, aristocratic, light-blond hair, blue eyes, a long and narrow face, a high nose, handsome, tall, well-behaved, clever, and relatively powerful before whatever happened one year ago. Or, to put it simply, this man had as much resemblance to Lord Grindelwald himself in his youth as an ordinary wizard could be.

-Presenting me with this man, ah, the Brits are seriously up to something.

After the guards were done with untying Lucius's hands from the small opening in the large iron door, and closed it from behind, the younger blond nodded politely to the elder one, and spoke with a clear British accent: "Guten Morgen, Lord Grindelwald."

-Nah, he needs to improve his German.

In order to avoid any misunderstandings caused by the British aristocrat's substandard German, Grindelwald spoke in impeccable English, and gestured to his guest room, "Good morning, Mr. Malfoy. If it were not too bothersome to you, could you change into the clothes I prepared for my guests? - One can hardly believe what the naughty boys might have done to the prison uniforms."

-And the orange color, eww, what an eyesore!

As his guest was changing into proper wizarding robes in the guest room, Grindelwald briefly amused himself by contemplating what the new prison guard Alexander Dimitrov might have tried to apply to Lucius' clothes and his body.

-That guy conceals it well, yet the sense of danger radiating from him is unmistakable. Let me see what kind of entertainment this dark-lord-wannabe would offer me within the next two months.

After Lucius exited the guest room, Grindelwald applied several wandless privacy spells that he could legally use, plus some wordless and wandless extra, and then nodded to the younger blond.

The British aristocrat half-bowed to Lord Grindelwald, "Lord Grindelwald, I am here to deliver our sincere gratitude for what you have done for the peace of Great Britain."

Grindelwald showed Lucius the sofa, and casually said, "Ah, that. I suppose one shouldn't credit oneself too much for what one has done for one's own territory."

The British aristocrat's mask might have cracked a bit, but he quickly collected himself, and claimed, "Lord Grindelwald, with all due respect, we spoke truth about Lord Dumbledore's conditions."

-OK, he is not here to surrender. Farewell, my best case scenario. To be honest with myself, if the Brits are really about to give up on their knees, I suppose the Americans might be a better choice. With seven hypocritic and squabbling lords and ladies, the Brits might be able to wiggle out something in resemblance to freedom.

"And for some reason, the British wizards either cannot or would not extract Albus from Time." Grindelwald pointed out the obvious facts, "From a certain point of view, I suppose Great Britain is indeed safer when the rest of the world has no idea about Albus' true condition, for the unknown is usually more terrifying than the known. However, I wonder how much longer Great Britain can hide behind Albus' reputation."

Lucius smiled bitterly, "I suppose, we can establish some new reputations."

"Such as?" Grindelwald was somewhat intrigued.

-The annoying Brits, you may never know how many ancient relics they possess. In the name of Atlantis, why was Merlin born in Britain?

"Miss Hermione Jane Granger, or the so-called Girl-Who-Revived, bears some great resemblance to a unicorn." Lucius provided.

"Ah, so you are here to claim that the rumor on the side-effects of unicorn blood is true, and you want me to deliver this news to the rest of the world." Grindelwald reasoned. "And why should I believe you? Or, regardless of my personal belief, why should I slip such indications to the interested ears?"

"Tom Morfin Riddle can attest to the less than pleasant after-effects of unicorn blood." Lucius' lips twisted into a sly smile.

Grindelwald remembered the rumors about the slayed unicorns in Hogwarts before that night. He couldn't help but smiled to himself.

-Ah, my dear old Albus, always so good at traps.

Grindelwald didn't plan to say that he was somewhat convinced by the evidence. He asked, "Whatever lead to the temporary re-disappearance of this Riddle, I do believe he has recently made another round of return, hasn't he? Or, since you were supposedly there, could you enlighten me on what indeed happened that night?"

Lucius' smile turned bitter again. "Lord Grindelwald, my tongue is tied on this matter. However, I can disclose that there was indeed a sacrificial ritual involved."

Grindelwald contemplated this answered, and wondered what Albus had done. He knew Albus had access to the Hall of Prophecy, and a true seer Trelawney was among the Hogwarts staff, therefore Albus could often make some bizarre movements and somehow let everything go his way. This made deducing Albus' plots very difficult, even for the person who knew him best.

-With the help from the information passed to him by Time, the so-called "sacrificial ritual" could be as simple as an Unbreakable Vow!

-Oh, wait.

Grindelwald eyed the weak wizard in front of him, "Is it an Unbreakable Vow?"

The younger blond answered without a blink, "Lord Grindelwald, with all due respect, I can neither confirm nor deny your current speculation, or any speculation in this nature."

-Hmm, this does sound like an Unbreakable Vow. In the name of Atlantis, how did Albus defeat an enemy by an Unbreakable Vow? You can't simple take a vow and say you will defeat someone, and gain the power from the Vow. No Unbreakable Vow of such nature can stand, hardly anyone tried that survived from it. Or, did Albus discover some advanced-level Unbreakable Vow?

Then, Grindelwald's eyes sparkled: yes, there is indeed an advanced-level of Unbreakable Vow. Every Interdict powerful wizards imposed on this world is an advanced-level of Unbreakable Vow.

-Did Albus throw away his Time to make his Interdict stand? Or, did he use the lives and magic of the Flamels, Monroe, and the Death Eaters to do it?

-Lucius Malfoy's head was mercifully spared, with only part of his magic sacrificed, for he had changed his side before that night. And his wife was also returned to him. Oh, the treatment of Lucius Malfoy is so Albus.

-And what's the content of this Interdict? Anyone with serious attempts to the Stone and/or the Mirror is doomed?

-Or, is it what the Brits want me to think?

Grindelwald pondered on this question, while asking, "Is there any other message that you want to deliver to me?"

The British aristocrat who was busy studying Grindelwald's face answered. "That is all for now. Lord Grindelwald, is there anything that you want me to deliver back to the holder of Line of Merlin Unbroken?"

-Bones? That foolish woman? Or, did he mean Albus? Do they have some means to communicate with Albus?

Grindelwald considered the implications, and motioned his hand. He pointed to a stack of paper floating toward Lucius, and said, "My standard welcome package, of course. It contains some of my research results on magical reproduction. By the way, for your information, blood purity does make sense to a certain extent."

The younger blond's face went blank for an entire second before he could smile and reply, "Lord Grindelwald, I can hardly express our gratitude toward your generosity."

Before the British envoy to Nurmengard could utter more nonsense, Grindelwald told the ex-Lord Malfoy that he should take the current proper garments as a gift as well, and dismissed the talkative British aristocrat.

-Oh, Albus. Why did you never take my welcome package? Is it because you were so afraid that my research might invalidate your beloved political correctness that you refuse to see the truth? Without you meddling everything, I suppose the British wizarding society can finally enjoy the benefits that the rest of the wizarding society in the developed world had already enjoyed for almost fifty years, and see some increase in the number of the newborns.

-My dear old Albus, I would really like to see your face when you welcome the new generation of Grindelwald-method-born students.

Chapter 42: Nurmengard, Interlude, Ukraine

I would like to thank my beta, Kuilin.

8:10 am, July 19th, 1993 (Kiev Time)

In a small country villa outside of Kiev, Leonid Nikolayevich Smirnov twitched uncomfortably in the single person couch, his eyes jumped from furniture to furniture in the living room, and decidedly avoiding the direction of the fireplace. He swallowed down hard, regretting his decision to join the group of wizards who profited from selling Soviet Union's secret - an instant death might be easier than his current status, being the weakest and most dispensable member of the group, and assigned with the most dangerous task, which was to face the dangerous buyers, and to tell the secrets of powerful wizardry. Smirnov had no idea whether he would be tortured this time, or maybe either the buyers or the other wizards in the group might kill him afterwards.

Smirnov knew that ever since Soviet Union collapsed, every sensible country in the world, and a lot of intelligent self-aspiring wizards who wanted to walk the walks of great wizards, had tried their hands in this land. The United States had gotten the cream of the crop - they had directly recruited the best magical researchers, and two or three former Comrades (with a capital "C") were rumored to have been bought by the Americans. As for nations not as attractive as the United States, or individuals with deep pockets, buying secrets was a reasonable thing to do.

In most other countries, secrets of powerful wizardry were only known to powerful wizards. However, in the former Soviet Union, things had been a little different.

Long before the Great October Socialist Revolution in 1917, powerful Russian wizarding lords and ladies had a tradition to be heavily involved in Muggle politics. Lord Grigori Rasputin, the most powerful Russian wizarding lord at that time, had taken this tradition to an extreme: he had publically served as a healer and a top counselor in the Tsar's court, and had involved heavily with Muggle politics. Some of his advice, such as "don't go to war with Germany", was quite perceptive and sensible in hindsight; however, for the most part, he just enjoyed himself too much with alcohol and females (Muggles, witches, and magical creatures alike), gave irrational advice, and led the country into deeper and deeper disaster. Some magical historians had suspected that he was a true seer - after his attempts to prevent Russia from participating in World War I had failed, Lord Rasputin had foreseen the fall of the Romanov Dynasty and his own demise, and had thus lived every day as his last day on Earth. Lord Rasputin's acts had earned him well-deserved hatred from Muggle serfs to Muggle nobility, and from wizards to goblins. By the end of 1916, both Muggle aristocracy and other wizarding lords couldn't suffer him anymore, so they ganged up and assassinated him. It was said that before his assassination, Lord Rasputin had written to the Tsar, stating that in case he arrived at Serbia safely, then the Tsar had nothing to worry about; if he was killed by the commoners, the Romanov Dynasty might still have a few years; if he was killed by the nobles, then the Dynasty only had three months, and the Tsar's family had at most two years to live. The fates of the Romanovs soon proved Lord Rasputin's Prophecy, that after he was assassinated in December, 1916, the February Revolution in 1917 overthrew the Romanov Dynasty, and the Tsar's entire family were executed by the communists in July, 1918.

After Lord Rasputin's infamous example, the Comrades in Soviet Union chose to take a less conspicuous position in Muggle politics, yet they were still heavily involved in almost everything.

Comrade Mikhail Andreyevich Shakhov, the most powerful Russian wizard after Lord Rasputin, was an ardent believer of communism. As a contrast to Lord Rasputin, Comrade Mikhail Andreyevich (as he liked himself to be called) led an almost impeccable personal life - much more of a "saint" than "Father Grigori" ever was. Though Comrade Mikhail Andreyevich had wielded extraordinary power and influence in both the Muggle and wizarding Russian for more than sixty years, he lived an almost saintly life: mild, polite and modest toward his comrades, always helping out young wizards in need with his own money, only having an apartment in Moscow and a villa outside Moscow that was not much larger than the one Smirnov was currently in, and leaving behind a heritage less than a year's wage of a common worker when he passed away in 1982. Over the years, countless wizards had seen him and his wife joining the long lines in front of regular shops, waiting to buy food and supplies. According to the few times that Smirnov met Comrade Mikhail Andreyevich, Smirnov felt the aged wizard was quite sincere in his way. Not even his political enemies could accuse him of nepotism, avaricious, adultery, or even the most common sin for Russian males, alcoholism.

As for Comrade Mikhail Andreyevich's political life, that was a complete other matter. He was known to be as ruthless as winter in Russian toward the "Enemies of Soviet Union" - be them White Russian Army, Trotskyists, Grindelwald's Army, or political dissidents. After killing and ousting powerful wizards and witches who supported the White Army, Comrade Mikhail Andreyevich had single-handedly restructured Russian wizarding society. One of the result was that the majority of the wizarding working population had become members of Cheka, which was the predecessor of KGB and GRU.

Many wizards in the Soviet Union admired the level of freedom wizards in other countries enjoyed, and resented Comrade Mikhail Andreyevich for this reason. However, being a member of the KGB had suited Smirnov just fine - he wasn't much of a wizard anyway, and he just loved the bureaucracy and paper-pushing in the much larger Muggle government.

Smirnov's talent in bureaucracy, officialese, flattery, and choosing the right side - instead of his weak magic and average-level intelligence - had promoted him fast on the ladders of the KGB. By 47 years old, Smirnov had made himself a colonel, and had a clearance level that ranked just below the Comrades with a capital "C". Though Smirnov could hardly actually practise or even understand most of the secrets he had access to, they still made him feel quite good about himself.

Then, there came the biggest blow in Smirnov's professional and personal life: the collapse of Soviet Union. Although Smirnov, like more than 70% of Russian people, had voted to keep the Soviet Union, the Muggle politicians and a few Comrades on the top of the ladder still managed to dismantle the largest country in the world against people's will.

In December 1991, for the first time, Smirnov realized how powerless he was without the protection of the system: one of Lord Isaac Yodov's students, a relatively powerful witch whom he used to boss around for various official trivialities, kicked him out from the newly founded Ministry of Magic without a word.

With his savings going down fast in the hyperinflation that followed the collapse of Soviet Union, Smirnov really missed Comrade Mikhail Andreyevich: if the power Comrade hadn't died of old age in 1982, Soviet Union probably wouldn't have collapsed. According to rumors, Comrade Mikhail Andreyevich had helped the Muggle politicians in their effort to oust Khrushchev. Therefore, Comrade Mikhail Andreyevich might just oust Yeltsin, Gorbachev and their lot as well.

Without any useful skills in the new world, Smirnov doubted whether he and his family could survive the winter in 1992. Therefore, when the group of wizards who sold top magical secrets of the great country to anyone with a deep pocket approached Smirnov, he didn't have much of a choice (and they wouldn't give him any). Smirnov had everything they desired: dispensable, easily manageable, weak in magic, three kids to be threatened with, and a suitable identity to convince the buyers the secrets were authentic.

Smirnov sighed, and dearly hoped that the two wizards who claimed that they were from Canada wouldn't kill him afterwards; or if they try, the relatively powerful wizards in the group would promptly come and help.

The fireplace suddenly flared up, and two blurry figures wearing black robes walked out from the green flames.

As both of them walked toward the sofa, one of the figures spoke with a distorted sound: "Good morning, Mr. Smirnov. Let's begin by what you learned after you graduated Koldovstoretz Magical School."

Obviously, neither of those two even considered the courtesy as giving pseudonyms of themselves to a nobody such as Smirnov.

If the KGB school Smirnov attended after Koldovstroretz had forced him to learn one thing, that would be foreign languages - another reason why the group chose him to face the buyers.

Smirnov swallowed, and nervously replied in English with some Russian accent, "My name is Leonid Nikolayevich Smirnov. After Koldovstroretz, I received two years of education in Shakhov Vocational School, which actually taught us wizards things about the KGB and GRU. After that, I joined the KGB. Ever since my graduation, I worked in the Administrative and Regulatory Department of the Twenty-third Chief Directorate - or, you can call it the Secretive Magical Chief Directorate. My main responsibility was on the regulatory authorizations of magical researches. I had a rank of colonel, with a Clearance Level 3."

"I heard, every Russian wizard had to learn how to serve the Muggle government?" The figure on the left asked. Even the distortion charm he or she applied on his sound couldn't mask his incredulity.

"Yes." Smirnov swallowed. "We also had to swear to be loyal to Soviet Union, and never reveal its secrets. - No, we didn't take the Unbreakable Vow, because it was impossible to find enough wizards to sacrifice their magic to make the Vow stand for everyone. Comrade Mikhail Andreyevich, I mean, Comrade Mikhail Andreyevich Shakhov, had made a Hammer. The Hammer had similar functions to the Goblet of Fire, or maybe it was a little weaker. We just needed to write down our oath, and punch the parchment with the Hammer to make our oath stand. And, and, I can only release the secrets to you now, because -"

Smirnov choked a bit as he said the next sentence: "Because Soviet Union doesn't exist anymore."

Although this probably wasn't the first time Smirnov had said it, he was still submerged by a wave of sadness. He missed the decent job, the generous salary, the government car, the decent apartment in Moscow, his villa outside Moscow, government-paid heating bills, the government-paid vacations to the beaches by Black Sea and to Yugoslavia, the privileges he had…

-And what am I now? A foreigner in Kiev. Ukraine. Kiev, for the sake of Merlin, the Holy Lady, or whoever! Kievan Rus, the very place the Slavic people originated. Isn't this ridiculous?

Yes, Smirnov did miss the Soviet Union, and it was not only for monetary reasons.

However, the two "Canadians" obviously didn't care much about Smirnov's sentiments. Their interest was completely on another matter: "You claim that Shakhov had made a Hammer, that is similar to the Goblet of Fire. Do you know how it is made? Do you know the secrets of it?"

Smirnov shook his head: "No, it was beyond my clearance level. Only the Comrades with a capital 'C' know that."

"Hmm, interesting." The figure sitting on the left tapped his wand.

Smirnov almost screamed: "Don't torture me! You can use Legilimency on me, and look for it yourselves."

"Don't panic yet. Legilimency can wait for a while. Now go on." The figure on the left side demanded.

"What we learned from Koldovstroretz and Shakhov Vocational School was rather basic. There was nothing that was forbidden by the Interdict of Merlin. I have copies of my textbooks from Shakhov Vocational School here, you can take a look." Smirnov pointed to the stack of books beside him.

The figure on the right summoned the books, and began to check them for any hostile magic. When he or she was done, these two figures began to flip through the books.

The figure on the left exclaimed, "Ah, you Russians have measured the speed of travel by Floo, Apparition, and Portkey? Fascinating. And the travel time for all three methods is - what does it mean here?" The blurry figure pointed to something, and asked the figure on the right.

The figure on the right explained to his partner in several double blurred sentences.

-Doesn't every modern wizard already know about this? It is so simple that even I remember it, "t = a+d/c", where t is the time used, a is a method specific constant, d is the distance between two points, and c is the speed of light. Is the one on the left from Canada, or is he or she from a cave?

After a while, Smirnov heard the left figure said: "Have the Russian magical researchers measured the speed of travel by phoenix?"

Smirnov answered: "No, the only Russian witch who had a phoenix died in the war against Grindelwald, that was before our measurement instruments were accurate enough to do such measurements."

"Pity." The left one commented.

The right one asked: "Here, the textbook claimed that the absolute magic level of a wizard can be measured by the average random noise one induces while sleeping in a special room hooked with certain Muggle electronic devices. Can we get the design of the room and the electronic devices somewhere?"

Smirnov hoped that this would bring him some bonus from the group, and answered: "I don't have the design at hand, but we can surely give you one, for a proper price. As for the Muggle devices and magical materials needed, we can get them for you as well."

The right one replied: "Good. Since you Russians have used Muggle electronics to measure the amount of magic in a wizard, have you figured out why magic interferes with Muggle electronics?"

Smirnov finally heard a question that he knew from his work in KGB, and answered: "No, but some magical researchers have doubted that it was an artificial effect caused by some half-failed Interdict."

"Interdict? By who? What's the content of the Interdict?" The left one asked agitatedly.

The right one added: "What do you think you know, and how do you think you know it?"

Smirnov had a strange feeling about the right one's question. He had been trained to ask such questions in the KGB while interrogating suspects (though he had never actually interrogated anyone), and few wizards had asked such questions - not that he could remember much. He replied: "I learned the information from an internal seminar presented by one of our magical researchers, - I think he and his whole research group are in the United States now. He stated that extensive double-blind experiments had shown that the presence of strong magic in or around non-magical animals and Muggles had almost zero effect on any physiological parameters of the test subjects, or the sense orientation of non-magical migrational birds, magic most likely doesn't have any effect on the electrochemical reactions, signaling of neurons, and, err, and things like that. It seemed that magic only affects manmade - OK, as well as goblins and other magical beings made - electronics. This can hardly be anything natural. Their conclusion was that most likely some powerful wizard in the beginning of the Second Industrial Revolution imposed this effect onto the world. You know, the whole 'development of technology or magic can destroy the world' thing, quite popular with the old-fashioned Brits, I heard. Anyway, if that was the aim of the one who imposed this on the world, his or her work was probably partially botched, for the Muggles still developed very powerful electronics and nuclear weapons."

The sound Smirnov heard became double-blurred again. After a while, the one on the right asked: "Has anyone figured out a way to mitigate the effects of magic on electronics?"

Smirnov answered: "Not to my knowledge. However, some have suspected that the effect is only limited to the Earth, or the surface of the Earth. I heard that according to some non-conclusive data, if they put some magical devices and some signal generating Muggle electronics together in a satellite, the signal received on the ground gets better as the satellite gets away from the ground. There are rumors that the Americans wanted to try this in their missions to the moon, but the first trial failed spectacularly, killing several astronauts, so neither they nor we have tried this with any manned mission - or any mission too important - again."

"Oh." The left one exclaimed, but the sound soon became blurred again.

Smirnov was never too keen on magic, but even he knew this meant that the Interdict of Merlin can be bypassed by going to the moon - that's what some magical researchers had claimed, anyway.

After a while, the figure on the right asked another question: "What do you know about very intelligent magical creatures, such as veelas, goblins, acromantulas, etc.?"

This was another question that Smirnov knew the answer from his work in KGB. "A lot of our researchers thought they are human beings with inheritable curses. Or, at least, a group of researchers managed to transfigure a quintaped to a sapient man, very violent, though. You know, when powerful wizards can transfigure stones to the body of human beings, but the transfigured thing was never intelligent. Therefore, the man-eating quintapeds must be intelligent on their own accord, and the rumor that the reason they are like this was a curse is probably true."

Then, there came another round of blurred sound.

The next question came as: "Polyjuice potion, does it change the brain structure of the drinker to that of the person whose hair is used?"

"Yes, and other internal organs as well." Smirnov replied, but he quickly added, "Grindelwald's people did this."

As one question lead to another, they finally asked Smirnov the ultimate question: "What is magic? Where does it come from?"

Smirnov had no idea where magic had come from, but he had some answers to the first question: "Before Gorbachev cut down our research funding, one of our research groups claimed to have some preliminary data to show that magic might be, err, wave-particle duality, - that's the phrase in English, - just like light. They applied for funding to construct instruments to verify their theory, but their funding application was denied. Now, the whole group are in the United States."

After some prolonged blurred sound, Smirnov heard the familiar incantation: "Legilimens."

Chapter 45: Space Travel Pt II, Possibilities

I would like to thank my beta, Kuilin.

6:13 am, July 21st, 1993

On and around Harry's desk in his trunk, stacks and stacks books on astronomy, astrophysics, history of space exploration, science fiction, and other related topics scattered all over the place.

After Harry copied down yet another equation that they might use later, he glanced at his mechanical watch, and wondered if this would be an acceptable time to wake everyone up. A bright ball of light appeared in front of Harry at this time. With the power of Severus' locket, there were only a limited number of people whose names were on a whitelist that could approach Harry with their Patronus, so this got to be something urgent. In Mad-Eye's raspy voice, the Patronus said: "Son, Lucius Malfoy requested an immediate meeting with you, stating that he thought of something rather important, and he refused to let me know."

Harry glanced down at his draft on the possible route to the Moon.

-Lucius can't guess out that we should go to the Moon, can he? No, shrewd as the ex-Lord Malfoy is, he is not sharp on this kind of stuff. Something about Grindelwald, then.

Harry replied: "Send him in, my headquarter office."

-Hopefully, this isn't something about how Grindelwald might also know a Prophecy. Err, since Hermione and I decided not to reveal our guess to the rest of them, especially, not to someone meets Grindelwald on a daily basis, so if Lucius has thought of the same thing, he has every reason to consider this an important secret that he should only tell me.

-Geez. However, I do have to listen to what Lucius has to say, just in case that he has thought of some other important matters.

Harry reluctantly packed up his space travel plans, and sighed. Keeping so much secrets from almost everyone could be a burden, mentally, physically, and now, on his limited time budget as well. It was at these times, Harry understood why Dumbledore might appear to be a bit insane.

Harry trudged up the stairs, and left his trunk. He quickly washed, changed, and Floo-ed to his headquarter office with the Auror trio that was protecting him. Once in his office, Harry worked on the fireplace a bit to allow Mad-Eye and Lucius to come through, and the two quickly entered from the green flames.

As Mad-Eye was reluctantly applying protection and privacy charms around Harry and Lucius while excluding himself out, Harry sized up the blond who grew a special preference for the holding cell in DMLE ever since he guessed out that Grindelwald saw through their pretence of Dumbledore being around, and Voldemort might be among the guards. Harry couldn't help but to hold some distain upon the nobleman who cherished his own life so much, yet had cold-bloodedly killed at least seven others. However, since Lucius' mind was still useful now, and since he was Draco's father, Harry kept the feeling to himself.

After Mad-Eye was done with the spells, Lucius began in Parseltongue: "Lord Potter, ass I thought of Grindelwald'ss behavior yessterday, hiss urgentnesss jumped up a bit after he ssaw the advanced Patronuss. Thiss indicatess it had ssomething to do with the Patronuss, posssibly the powerful life magic in it. And hiss biggesst ssecret, whatever it iss, should be death magic. Maybe, the advanced Patronuss can block or interrupt the ritual that made him invincible."

Harry's mouth slightly opened: Ahh, that - that is another possibility, actually. And the chances aren't bad. This is indeed why we need a human expert on our side. On another thought, the true Patronus, plus Hermione's almost infinite vitality, should be able to block most death magic. Hmm, this is why I should always listen to my subordinates - they do come up with ideas that I have not thought of. I suppose, Lucius wouldn't dare to wake Voldemort up at 6 am, and tell him such important secrets.

Harry replied: "Thiss iss a very good guesss indeed, Mr. Malfoy."

To Harry's slight surprise, Lucius continued to reveal another important guess: "And the Elder Wand, which iss alsso called the Death Sstick, might have gained itss name for a reason."

Some human part of Harry instinctively wanted to reject the indication that the wand made by his ancestors could be used in something that evil, but the other parts of Harry knew better, so he kept his mouth closed.

Lucius hissed: "After I learned the Patronuss, Sseveruss had asked me a riddle, 'what cannot be killed?'At that time, it sseemed to me that the ansswer wass death. However, I don't really have the mental capacity to conquer death ass you and the Lady do."

Harry made a mental note to himself that he should tell Severus to be more discrete with important secrets with his best friend, no matter how much that black-haired man might want Lucius to live. And then, Harry's exceptional vivid imagination depicted a scene where he himself had to decide whether or not to reveal a secret to Hermione that could potentially save her life, and Harry found himself unable to withhold the information. Harry wasn't that sure whether he should lecture Severus anymore.

-In a sense, Severus had been a very lonely man, just like I was before I met Hermione. The friendship from the Malfoys might be the best thing ever happened to him since, err, since my mother broke up with him. Moreover, Severus has saved Lucius a couple dozen times, which might also contribute to his protectiveness toward Lucius.

Then, Harry remembered what happened when another man forced Severus to face the possibility of his best friend's death.

Harry felt cold sweat running down his spines: Thanks to Hermione, I am NOT Voldemort, and I will not become Voldemort.

Lucius' words continued without Harry's input: "Lasst night, as I thought over it, I realized that people might think there iss another thing that could not be killed - ssomeone or ssomething between life and death, for example, a wizard without a pounding heart."

And then Harry got it. From the tale of The Warlock's Hairy Heart, a powerful wizard could survive without a pounding heart for quite a while. From what Antioch Peverell understood of life and death, someone without a heart yet still breathing and thinking could be considered "between life and death". Probably, Antioch took out his own heart, made it into the core of the Elder Wand. Considering himself incapable of being killed, Antioch used the Elder Wand to challenge Death, and failed - the killing curse could kill everything with a brain, not everything with a heart.

Lucius' guesses added another layer to the story: "If the taless about the Peverell brotherss are true, then the brotherss musst have dessigned powerful magic to conquer Death. Probably, the wand with the core of a breathing human'ss heart can alsso be conssidered ass ssomething between life and death, and wieldss the power to transsform death magic into other typess of magic. In thiss way, Antioch Peverell could utilize the almosst infinite magic from Death, he also thought that he couldn't be killed by Death, and he tried."

-Oh wait, Voldemort knew how to summon Death with a rope which has hanged a man and a sword which has slayed a woman. He might have gained this knowledge from Slytherin's pet snake, and Salazar might gain this knowledge from his ancestors, the Peverell brothers. It all fits.

Harry briefly imagined the sad scene that his powerful and brilliant ancestor made the Death Stick with his own heart, how he summoned Death himself, how he bravely dueled with the last enemy of any sapient being, and how his misconception about life and death became the fatal error in his plan. However, since Death didn't devour all human beings more than one thousand years ago, probably Antioch had sent Death back to wherever it belonged before he died.

Lucius stayed silent for a while, as if mourning for Antioch together with Harry, and then continued: "Grindelwald might have ussed the Death Sstick to transsform the death magic produced by the killing of Muggless to hiss own magic, and hence made himsself invincible."

Harry had to admit, Lucius' deduction made a lot of sense. Actually, his deduction made too much sense.

-Is this the advantage of having a genuinely dark wizard on our side? Or is it another incident with the "Protego Vitamaxima"?

-However, if this is Voldemort again, why did he tell us this? Learning to be nice?! No, this is way too nice.

-On the other hand, Lucius is indeed a human expert, and it is this man who came up with the original idea about the Elder Wand and the Malfoy's family wand before.

Harry searched the blond wizard's face, and found that Lucius looked at him in an expectant way.

-Oh, right. I have promised him that I would negotiate a one hundred years deduction in prison sentence if he finds out what Grindelwald's secret is.

-Don't tell me that Voldemort told Lucius the secret, because he wanted Lucius to have a shorter prison sentence. That is simply ridiculous!

-Ah, I know someone with this motive. Severus Snape. Severus might have left hints in Lucius' mind, memory charmed Lucius, and probably also memory charmed himself.

Harry didn't quite know what to do with the black-haired wizard who was probably too loyal to his best friend by this point. Harry breathed in, and breathed out.

"Mr. Malfoy, if everything you ssaid -" Harry glanced at Lucius who was about to protest, and changed his sentence, "If the gisst of thiss iss verified, I will hold my sside of the bargain."

Chapter 46: Space Travel Pt III, Lord Slytherin's Favorite Morning Radio

I would like to thank my beta, Kuilin.

7:22 am, July 21st, 1993

In his new secret chamber in Hogwarts, tuned in for his favorite "radio channel (as the current wizards called it)" from "Harry Potter's" headquarter office, Lord Salazar Slytherin sat in a couch whose comfort level just didn't exist in his time, and enjoyed his breakfast: a roasted tomato, baked potatoes, and fried eggs. Salazar found the novel food items, - such as tomatoes and potatoes, which were unknown to the Europeans back in his time, - quite pleasant to eat.

Again, Salazar felt that locking himself up in the Mirror was the best decision he had ever made. Of course, Salazar didn't just mean the food and furniture, he was primarily referring to the powerful magic he learnt in this new era - for example, the one that "Harry Potter" was currently telling the unicorn girl what Lucius revealed to him.

Although Salazar was dissatisfied by Lucius' failure in Draco's linguistic education, he did have to credit Lucius for his intuition and human skills for figuring out the hypothesis that the improved Patronus could interrupt the death magic that had once made Grindelwald invincible. However, the need for a magical item that transcended life and death as an intermediary was definitely not Lucius' original idea. Salazar was quite sure of that, because, well, he himself was the one who actually thought of it during the so-called "brainstorm" with Severus last night.

After guessing out this important secret, Salazar wanted to test whether it was true as quickly as possible. Unfortunately, Salazar didn't have any wand that was made of the heart of a human being at hand, but he knew where to get one.

To be honest, it was a bit embarrassing for Salazar to temporarily borrow a gift that he gave to his descendants without notifying the rightful owner, especially, when another descendant - who also happened to be the owner's godfather - was watching. Salazar had to hiss to Severus to promise that he would return the wand to little Draco the moment he was done, so that Severus would stop looking at him in that way.

The Boy-Who-Lived had kept two dementors in Hogwarts as a Voldemort killer, so these unpleasant creatures became safe and convenient lesser substitutes for Death himself. Salazar and Severus slipped into the room where the dementors were guarded by two Auror trio, and Salazar knocked down all the Aurors in one blow. Salazar grabbed one of the cages containing the dementors, and Apparated back to his new secret chamber together with Severus.

With Severus getting ready to block the dementor anytime if things went wrong, Salazar tried to give the dementor mental commands. After a number of failures, Salazar observed a horrified magical twitch from the dementor when he was determined that he would protect the world from being destructed by the Muggles, as if the shadow of death was trying to refuse this possibility. Salazar thought for a while, and then tricked his mind into another mentality: Shadow of Death, you know the advanced Patronus can banish you, so help yourself by lending me some of your power, or you won't exist.

Salazar did feel a bit of death magic the dementor was reluctantly streaming toward his way then. However, even if Salazar knew he could transform the death magic into neutral magic with Armand's heart, still fresh and sort of "alive" after so many years, contacting such dirty magic was still highly uncomfortable.

Salazar signaled to Severus to let him use his Patronus to block the dementor for a while, so that Salazar would be able to think. With Severus' bright ball of Patronus, the death magic the poor shadow of Death was still streaming toward Salazar was blocked. Severus seemed to be uncomfortable upon the contact, while the empty cloak representing death rolled and twisted painfully in the air.

-Ah, the stream of death magic can be blocked by our version of improved Patronus. Therefore, the better Patronus wielded by my crazy descendant and the unicorn girl must be more powerful toward this kind of magical streaming.

Salazar thought for a while, then signaled Severus to stop. Salazar pointed the Malfoy family wand toward the death magic stream, and willed it to absorb the death magic. Salazar felt death magic entering the wand, and the wand - or Armand's heart - screamed that it resented the dirty magic. Salazar waved the wand to cast "Lumos". A bright light ball larger than the head of a troll rushed out of the wand, and Severus quickly dodge away from the should-be-faint light ball dashing like a cannon shell. The light ball smashed into the opposite wall, and several pieces of shattered stone slabs flew out from the surface of the magically reinforced solid stone wall.

Severus asked in disbelief: "Iss that a Lumoss?"

Salazar mentally willed the dementor to stop, and looked down at the wand in amazement, and, err -

Severus' eyes also turned to the Malfoy family wand.

To Salazar's great embarrassment, the oak wand carefully maintained by generations of Malfoys over the past one thousand years had developed quite some visible cracks.

-Damn it! Oak is for life and affinity to magic, while yew is the proper container for death.

Salazar quickly examined the core of the wand, and found that Armand's heart was luckily unhurt. Realizing Severus also noticed the cracks, Salazar hissed awkwardly: "I am an exceptional wand maker. Shall repair and improve it before returning it to little Draco. Wrong type of wood. I shall not usse it again."

Severus paused for a while, and then commented: "Impresssive magic."

While Salazar was busy repairing and improving the Malfoy family wand with magic that he invented after he made this particular wand, he started to wonder if he had been too soft to his descendants.

-I have probably told Severus too much, and Draco may later discover that the wand becomes better. Maybe the Stone can't fix softness caused by old age.

"Sso, iss thiss the ssecret?" Severus examined the wall, asking.

Salazar was glad that Severus was clever enough to omit the awkward part of tonight's experiment, so he explained to the descendant whom he was determined to memory charm soon: "Probably the German guy ussed a different mentality, making a deal with Death through a life eater or ssomething like that, while I threatened it. I ssupposse, having a trade can render the magic flow more controllable, while my method would drain a dirty creature out of exisstence in sseveral minutess. I need to work on the detailss of thiss for a while, in casse I need a power boosst for a short period ssometime later."

After Salazar properly managed the dementor and the Auror trios, he and Severus turned the Time-Turner twice and sneaked toward Draco's bed chamber. All this time, Severus seemed to be in some sort of emotional conflict.

"What?" Salazar asked.

Severus reluctantly answered, "The Boy-Who-Lived hass promissed to reduce Luciuss' prison time by one hundred yearss, in casse Lucius figuress out the ssecret. I know Luciuss deservess every minute of hiss ssentence, but -"

"You want to tell Luciuss thiss ssecret?" Salazar asked in disbelief.

Severus was quite embarrassed, "I -"

Salazar sighed inwardly: I do hope my descendants are friendly toward each other, but this is too much. Did Lucius treat his bastard brother so well, that after Severus brought Lucius back from death, Severus still feels that he needs to get a shorter prison sentence for Lucius? Although I think Lucius should be rewarded, instead of being locked up for killing Muggle-lovers, this -

Salazar then realized three things that he needed to do: First, I need to get a heart willingly taken out from someone's chest; second, I'd better undermine Severus and Lucius' loyalty to the so-called "Boy-Who-Lived", so that they won't stick to this crazy descendant after I reveal the truth to them; and third, I have to test and see if this crazy descendant would try to make a deal with Death, and I shall kill him the instance he prepares the ritual.

-Hmm, I should put something on the Death Stick, so that I shall be notified if it absorbs any death magic.

-No, to be safe. I should link the Death Stick to my set of triggers on the Mirror, so that once my crazy descendant tries to sacrifice a lot of lives, and to transform death magic to other types of magic with it, all Riddles would be locked up in the Mirror.

-Yes, this would be Riddle's first and possibly only test. If the younger Riddle - or anyone else, for that matter - decides to kill a lot of Muggles to gain infinite power, according to what Severus explained to me several times, and what I now conjecture, may lead to Muggles to use the ritual weapon. Therefore, I should modify the trigger on the Mirror, so that if any wielder of the Death Stick tries to make a deal with Death, they would be locked in Time.

Then, another idea came to Salazar: As a matter of fact, since the younger Riddle already incorporated the Shadow of Death a part of the set of triggers to lock himself up (with my help, of course), by threatening them, I should further threaten the dementors, so that if anyone tries to make a deal with Death by mass sacrifice - not only restricted to the use of the Death Stick - he or she would be locked up in Time. Hmm, this magic would take me a few days to perfect, but it is definitely doable.

"Alright, let'ss go to the sso-called Ministry of Magic after returning the wand to little Draco, and talk to Luciuss." Salazar hissed.

Severus' eyes opened wide in amazement and gratefulness.

With Severus leading the way, Salazar breaking the sham of magical wards in the Ministry of Magic like a breath (with a few exceptions in DMLE, which took Salazar a few minutes), they sneaked into the temporary holding cell in no time.

After stunning Lucius - in case the blond made some unwise moves - Salazar woke him up. Lucius seemed to be first confused and horrified by the situation, but after Salazar removed his previous memory charm, realization began to show on Lucius' face. All of a sudden, Lucius shot Severus a grateful look.

Salazar didn't want to pander on the question that how much the blond had guessed out. He cursed his softness again, and asked with a straight face: "Luciuss, what do you think of the matterss of yessterday?"

Salazar knew Severus was mouthing "speak truth" behind his back. Since this would help with their conversation, Salazar ignored it.

Lucius then revealed what he thought of before he fell asleep, that Grindelwald's eagerness jumped up after he saw the Granger girl's Patronus, and the ritual might be tempered with the powerful life magic.

To Salazar's amazement, what Lucius got from reading Grindelwald was quite accurate, while Severus and Salazar himself only got this point from experiments with a dementor.

-Good boy, Lucius. Grandpa Salazar shall reward you for this.

Salazar pulled out a newly made hat from his pouch, and put the hat on his head. Salazar could feel the excitement and happiness flowing out of the wizard behind him the moment he took out the hat, and Salazar annoyingly admitted that he was spoiling his descendants again.

Salazar sighed inwardly, put the hat and a gold coin on the ground, and casted "Avada Kedavra" toward the hat. A few incantations later, Lucius became much harder to kill.

When Salazar packed the hat and the gold coin up, he allowed Severus to explain the situation to Lucius. Of course, Salazar interrupted at the last part, and only revealed the proper segments of the secret to Lucius.

To Salazar's delight and slight embarrassment, Lucius proved that he was much sharper in human stuff than Severus was. The blond took in a breath, and said: "Lord Sslytherin, there iss no word that can expresss my gratitude. If there iss anything that I can do for you, pleasse do assk. For example, I ssupposse, a new wand might prove handy for the tassk? It would be my great honor, if my heart can be ussed for thiss great purposse."

-Oh, Lucius is clever. I didn't insinuate that oak was not proper for the ritual, nor did I mention that I broke and repaired Malfoy family wand in my experiment. Hmm, I suppose Lucius wants to make sure that Draco always has the Malfoy family wand at hand, so he proposed that I should make a new one with his heart. And he probably also wants me to feel guilty.

The irritating part of the matter was, although Salazar had made sure that Lucius couldn't be killed by something such as losing a heart, one of his initial aims to be here was to obtain Lucius' heart, and he knew exactly what game Lucius was playing, Salazar still felt a bit of guilt toward this sneaky descendant.

"Wha- "Severus hissed in horror, and then quickly said, "Ssalazar, you have made me a horcrux ass well, sso I -"

Although Salazar did predict that Lucius had the highest probability of getting maimed or killed by either Grindelwald or one of the Tom Riddles, he couldn't rule out the possibility that either Severus or himself would be in a better position to undergo the unpleasant process of handing out the heart before Lucius did, so he said: "Nah, don't fight for thiss now, whichever of the three of uss here needss the usse of the Sstone for other reasons firsst winss. And now, Luciuss, I shall memory-charm you, sso that you would reveal certain ssecretss to the Boy-Who-Lived, and ssee if he keepss hiss promisse."

-And to see how "Harry Potter" treats the friendship between his subordinates.

A few hours later, Salazar was in his new secret chamber, listening to the younger Riddle's moral dilemma.

The "boy" said: "Hermione, I need to tell you more about what I think happened with Lucius, before I can tell you what occurred to me around 3 am this morning, so that you won't be overwhelmed by my grand plan. I think the 'Patronus can interrupt the death ritual' part is probably Lucius' original idea. Actually, it is quite obvious in retrospect, and Lucius is an expert in reading human. However, I suspect that Severus told Lucius the second part, or at least he gave Lucius hints on it, then he memory-charmed both of them, so that Lucius can get a reduction in prison sentence."

The self-righteous unicorn girl replied with some moral nonsense, just as Salazar expected.

The young Riddle sighed: "Hermione, the problem is, we don't have any evidence, and Lucius did figure out the similarity between the Malfoy family wand and the Elder wand himself, so my guess isn't really well grounded. I would only assign it with at most seventy percent probability. And OK, Hermione, you can scream to me now, for I - , err, maybe I have read too much books with the high level villains giving orders to their subordinates in elusive ways, and while dealing with Lucius, I subconsciously lead myself into it. Well, when I talked to Lucius about his mission to weasel out Grindelwald's biggest secret, I asked Lucius to 'by any means that neither endangers the world, nor carries a prison sentence more than two years, figure out why Grindelwald had been invincible'. Back then, I was thinking on bribery, Confundus, or some other minor infringements of law. Therefore, even if my guess is correct, Lucius has figured it out by being friends with Severus - which is entirely legal - I am still responsible for getting him an one-hundred-year deduction in prison sentence. And by the way, I have also promised Lucius that in case he figures out Grindelwald's secret, I will not allow anyone to charge him with any other past crimes that didn't involve the death or permanent mental damage to sapient beings. Yeah, I am trapped by my own words this time. I should have realized that someone like Lucius Malfoy will definitely abuse any loopholes, and next time, I would be more careful with my promises with anyone."

While the self-righteous half-unicorn uttered more nonsense, Salazar thought: What? The younger Riddle does feel obliged to keep his words?! Hmm, judging from Severus' and Lucius' first interactions with me, I thought Tom Riddle was entirely unworthy of a leader of any kind. Is the younger Riddle acting this way, because he thinks this fits his current mask? This is madness beyond my imagination.

The younger Riddle accepted the Granger girl's critic, and said: "My major concern is, how should I treat the friendship between Severus and the Malfoys? Whether Severus is innocent in this incident or not, he probably did give the riddle containing the secret of the true Patronus to Lucius. I realize that Severus is probably more loyal to the Malfoys than to me, and he probably has some problems with withholding information from people he really likes. I suppose, from a human perspective, there is nothing wrong with holding your friends and godson in a higher position than the leader you serve because, err, because you don't want the world to be destroyed by the leader, I guess. And since I have never announced any rules, nor has Severus ever formally sworn loyalty, I can hardly call it betrayal even if Severus did leave some hints to Lucius. Hermione, when I made up a hypothetical scene in my head, that by not telling you some secret, you are, say, ten percent more likely to die, I would probably tell you some hints about the secret even if I know the secret might be dangerous. And in another entirely hypothetical scene, - Hermione, I know you would never do what Lucius did - say, you are found guilty for, err, causing severe head injuries to innocent bystanders in an unavoidable situation, I would definitely cheat the system in order to get you out of jail sooner. Hermione, I know this might be unfair to you, but you are the reason that I am not You-Know-Who, and we both know You-Know-Who's decision to dismiss Severus' request for Lily's life to be spared had lead to, could you tell me what should I do with Severus and Lucius?"

-Ha, tossing your hard decision to your subordinates? What a sham! Godric never did this. However, what does "you are the reason that I am not You-Know-Who" mean? Does this horcrux of Tom Riddle really think that he is an independant character? Did Tom Riddle make some original discoveries with horcrux that he didn't tell Nagini? Could he really cut off only pieces of his character from himself as some religious mudbloods suggested, that making horcrux was splitting your soul, and you could cut some characters off from yourself?

Salazar remembered that Severus once said Tom Riddle grew up in a Muggle Catholic orphanage, therefore Tom Riddle did know Muggle religion, and he could very well shape his inventions according to some ideas he learnt when he was young.

Just as Salazar began to wonder what would happen if this younger Riddle did contain most of the "good" characters of the original Tom Riddle (which the original one clearly didn't have much), the unicorn girl finished her hesitation, and said: "I am OK with the fact that Lucius and Severus are friends. And since you said you probably would do the same things for me, I guess I shouldn't raise my moral bar too high for Severus. Telling Lucius the riddle on the true Patronus might be acceptable. However, if your guess is right, this means Severus' moral standards aren't that high. Severus Snape joined the Death Eaters when he knew they were evil, and I am sorry Harry, he only abandoned his cause because the life of the woman he loved was threatened. He might have changed during the years he served Dumbledore, but he left us the first instance he thought Lily's death was revenged, to seek power of his own - not that there is anything wrong with it, you even encouraged him to do so. I don't want to raise the moral bar too high, but on the other hand, Mad-Eye stayed, - even after he regained his youth and his leg. Mad-Eye probably has never thought of resuming his dream to become a top wizard, he just stayed and protected us and the Stone. And I know, with the Russian textbooks and secrets, both of us agree that Severus is probably more useful than Mad-Eye. If Severus did leave hints to Malfoy, then Mad-Eye is definitely more trustworthy than Severus. Mad-Eye serves you because he is doing the right thing, while as you said, Severus serves you because he doesn't want the world to be destroyed. I don't mean that Severus is serving you for a wrong reason, but his reason isn't as right as Mad-Eye's, neither are his moral standards. Therefore, my suggestion is, first, let's try to find out what indeed happened. If that isn't possible, well, although due procedures call for us to assume that people are innocent unless proven guilty, we do need to observe Severus and Lucius more closely. As for Malfoy's prison sentence, let's defer the decision until we know what happened, or after we know it is impossible to know the answer, or, at least, after we know whether they are the true secrets of Grindelwald's invincibility."

Salazar almost seethed in fire: To "know it is impossible to know the answer"? You can use this excuse to defer it forever. What a detestable power-hungry mudblood bitch! You know the world is safe only when all Riddles are locked in Time, while you and Draco are assigned to be in charge. If Draco is going to hold you responsible for the younger Riddle's words to get Lucius the reduction in prison sentence, you may use the younger Riddle's guess today as an excuse to drive Draco out of power! And, is this why the younger Riddle ask this self-righteous Mudblood half-unicorn? So he has an excuse not to give Lucius his commutation? Or that he wants the Mudblood to have a weapon to deprive Draco of his power and/or his Father? Probably, this younger Riddle isn't the embodiment of the good characters of the original Riddle after all.

The younger Riddle hesitated for a while, and then said: "Hermione, yeah, you are right in a way. We do need to try out Lucius' ideas, and try to figure out what indeed happened, before deciding anything. I don't assume Grindelwald has left a written instruction manual lying anywhere, so we need to figure out the details ourselves. By 'ourselves', I mean Severus, Mad-Eye, you, and I. Unfortunately, Severus and Mad-Eye have quite a long list of things to figure out now. Moreover, I will have more urgent matters that would occupy their time very soon."

-Hmm, deferring difficult decisions. I guess he is just pretending to be good.

"OK, still on the current matter. From what might or might not happen yesterday, I notice that there is some severe problems with our current organization. First, our organization doesn't have any formal rules besides 'don't destroy the world' and 'obey Harry Potter', so that everyone is running on the rules of their own. This seems to be the general condition for most wizarding groups, but you and I should know better. And I suppose, Mad-Eye's rules are quite different from that of Severus', and that may be one of the reasons why they fight so much. Hermione, you and I need to make up some rules. Since Lucius is so good at abusing any loopholes, Draco and Lucius should be the ones to examine the rules for loopholes, and I can hold them responsible if anyone abuses the rules in ways that they should have thought of; Mad-Eye is good at security stuff, so he should be the one to safety-check everything; you should check on the moral stuff; and I should check the sanity of the rules."

Salazar listened to Harry's analysis of his organization, and found it quite reasonable. Lord Slytherin had lead wars against enemies many times, but he had never quite thought the organizational stuff as thoroughly as this younger Riddle did. Abusing the loopholes by subordinates? Sure. Salazar clearly remembered what an expert Armand was at this - even better than Salazar himself. However, Salazar had never thought of letting Armand criticing all the possible loopholes of the rules to be made.

Harry continued: "Moreover, we are in severe shortage of manpower - we rely on Severus and Mad-Eye on almost anything of real importance. I know we can trust Professor McGonagall's integrity, but since she is not a perfect Occlumens, so I can't tell her much of anything. The same goes for Professor Lupin. Kingsley Shacklebolt is a perfect Occlumens, but we don't know him much beyond Mad-Eye's words, and his current job to protect the Muggle Prime Minister is of vital importance as well. Besides them, the Order of Phoenix doesn't have any competent and clear-thinking wizards. I mean, Mr. and Mrs. Weasley are relatively powerful, but they are more like, you know, Ron, instead of the twins. Mrs. Malfoy and the Tonks are potential allies, but none of them is a perfect Occlumens, either. In the long run, we need to set up a training program, probably lead by Severus and Mad-Eye, so that we can train our people to be perfect Occlumens, while I can teach them on the rationality stuff, and you on the morality rules. More importantly, in the rules that we are about to make, we need to include how to recruit new blood into the Order of Phoenix."

Salazar found that he had never thought methods to train and recruit new bloods as thoroughly as the younger Riddle did.

-Riddle's previous organization, the Death Eaters, was not organized any better than what Godric and I did back in the old days. How come that this younger Riddle has so many better ideas? Oh, of course, Comrade Shakhov had gotten some thirty thousand wizards working for the same Muggle government organization , and it didn't collapse until nine years after his death, which performed much better than the Death Eaters did after the older Riddle disappeared for the first time. Shakhov might have left some hints on how he ruled Russian wizards in the textbooks. I haven't finished reading the textbooks yet, there are too many new concepts there. Severus is reading that stuff faster than I do, and I constantly need him to explain things to me. Hmm.

-Moreover, by "rules", does the younger Riddle mean the oath that you throw into the Goblet of Fire, or hit with the Hammer? It surely sounds like it.

Salazar decided that he needed to read the Russian textbooks faster, and to gain access to either the Goblet of Fire or the Hammer.

Just as Salazar began to wonder whether the Hammer was still in Moscow, the younger Riddle changed the topic, and revealed a great idea that almost made Salazar jumping from the couch.

-Going to the Moon, so that you can bypass the Interdict of Merlin?! I shall definitely help with this cause.

And the Boy-Who-Lived continued to reveal another great idea: "As for the origin of magic, Grindelwald has indicated it might have something about the Mirror and the Stone. I formulated some guesses on this subject this morning. Muggles and wizards alike have pretty much searched the entire planet, but nobody has ever found any ruins of a civilization that is greater than ours. However, there is the Mirror and the Stone, both are definitely way beyond Merlin's power. After I thought of the Moon idea, I just began to wonder if the Mirror and the Stone were from an alien civilization, that was millions or even billions of light years away from us, or even from another Universe. And when that civilization collapsed, the makers of the Mirror sent the Mirror and the Stone toward the stars, and they somehow landed on Earth many years ago. Since there are wizarding folks in almost every race, and legends from every civilization talked about lost civilization, I suppose they landed before homo sapiens left Africa. Well, since there are both magical plants and magical animals, they might arrived when all lives on Earth were single cells, and the Mirror and/or the Stone managed to 'tell' the story of a lost civilization to human beings afterwards. And there is also the possibility that our Earth is not the only planet where the Atlanteans left messages, and there might be other Mirrors and Stones on other planets - or still drifting in the Universe. Or maybe, the Atlanteans left other forms of messages somewhere - leaving everything to a single Mirror or a single form of messenger was way too risky. Therefore, by developing magic that can send us to the space, to explore other planets, suns, and galaxies, we might collect more relics, and know more about the Atlantis in general."

-Oh, this is such a wonderful idea. I shall spare the younger Riddle's life just for this contribution to all wizarding kind.

-Ah, wait, there is a test that I can run along the way. Hmm, I need to plant some hints in Severus' head now.

Chapter 47: Space Travel Pt IV, Biases of the Phoenix

I would like to thank my beta, Kuilin.

9:48 am, July 21st, 1993

"I have already asked Fawkes, and he has agreed to take this mission - thank Atlantis, Fawkes wasn't locked up in Time together with Headmaster Dumbledore." Harry petted the bird of fire perching on the armrest of his couch, and said to wide-eyed Draco, Severus, and Mad-Eye.

Severus slowly nodded: "I will go to Kazakhstan, then. Hopefully, Baikonur Cosmodrome is as badly managed as the rest of the former Soviet Union is. More importantly, I think I should be the one to go up to the Moon, instead of Miss Granger."

-Well, this is indeed a proposal that is entirely in character with Severus, self-sacrifice, and things like that. But, how should I phrase "I don't trust you enough for this mission"?

Before Harry could respond, Hermione said: "Professor Snape, as you already know, I am quite hard to kill, and I am probably blessed with a lot of luck."

"No, Miss Granger, we can't risk your life. Grindelwald and other top wizards in the world may not attack you, and a lot of them would even go as far as to personally protect you from harm, for they do not want the world to end by the retribution from the Universe. However, I am afraid that the vacuum, extreme temperature, meteoroids, and other things up there may not be as reasonable as the top wizards." Severus rebutted reasonably.

Mad-Eye also spoke up: "I agree with Severus on this. It is way too risky to let the lass go up there. However, I think I should be the one." He gave Severus and Draco a pointed look.

It seemed that Severus wanted to scoff, but that black-haired man checked his tongue as he had previously promised Harry that he would. Severus said instead: "I think there is a rather practical reason for me to go: I can understand or semi-understand written materials in fourteen different languages. I know this number is quite unimpressive when comparing to the records of the top wizards in the world, or even that of Crouch Sr., but this is the largest number among us. I think Minerva knows seven or eight, and how many do you know?" Severus politely glanced at Mad-Eye, as if it was an entirely innocent question.

Mad-Eye sent Severus an embarrassed and angry look, but he checked his tongue, and mumbled: "Four."

Harry remembered some of the notes he got from Albus and the Line of Merlin Unbroken. Those notes seemed like complete gibberish and doodlings to him. He couldn't even tell if the notes were written in English, Latin, Greek, Hebrew, or whatever languages - although Harry knew the letters of some of the possible languages looked quite different from that of English or Latin, he literally couldn't tell the difference from the notes.

-This is a very reasonable concern. We can't pre-select what notes to send up, so many of them might be written in languages that Hermione can't understand. If this can bypass the Interdict of Merlin, eventually, we have to send someone else up. For all I know, a lot of languages use Latin or Cyrillic alphabet, and it would be hard for someone without proper knowledge to tell the difference. Geez, I've heard that the current top wizards all speak hundreds of languages, do they even have time for anything else? Is this the reason that the development of magical society is so slow? Is it because all the clever people spend most of their time studying languages?

Harry wondered if he could trust Severus on such a mission, and he needed to buy some time before he figured out what to say. Therefore, Harry said instead: "Professor Snape, you must have realized, err, it is very dangerous up there, and, err -"

-For the sake of Atlantis, how should I properly phrase "you can't tell your best friend what you find up there, even if his brain depends on it"?

"Of course, Mr. Potter. The consecutive disasters with the Apollo 1 and the Soyuz 1 are considered to be the reason why neither the Soviets nor the Americans tried to send any wizards up to the space again. I suppose, it is much better to be the third wizard to die in a space mission than to die by the hands of You-Know-Who." Severus replied with a white face and a straight back, as if he was going to die the next moment.

Harry had to admit that Severus had his points. Harry suppose, getting killed by Voldemort would be a long and painful process, while death in a failed space mission would be much quicker, and it would involve much less pain. Moreover, to sacrifice your life in the mission to explore the Universe indeed carried much more meaning for the entire human race than getting yourself killed in some pathetic war among wizards.

Harry did a quick mental re-check on the information he just glanced over this morning: The failure of Soyuz 1 mission in April, 1967 sounded really like a series of electronic malfunctions caused by magic: the solar panel failed first, the orientation detectors followed, then stabilization system was gone, the parachute didn't unfold, and finally, the reserved parachute got entangled. As for how the Apollo 1 failed, err, I need to look it up.

-However, Severus probably has some misconceptions about the danger involved in space traveling. Well, according to information available to Severus, the two previous trials to send wizards up to the space both failed with disastrous results, so he expects himself to die as well. What he hasn't realized is that, in this mission, we do not rely on Muggle electronics, so it is much safer...

Hermione's head turned quickly toward the large window in Harry's office first, and then followed by Mad-Eye's magical eye.

"What the f-" The old Auror murmured.

The unfinished F-word from Mad-Eye pretty much expressed the same feeling Harry was experiencing, because he saw some red-golden fire appeared besides the sun, and it was dashing toward the window.

-A phoenix?!

The black-haired man also seemed to be stunned by this unexpected development. He stood there like a statue for a whole second, before he dashed toward the window to remove the anti-phoenix charms placed there.

-Ahh, the phoenix doesn't want to take Severus to the Moon immediately, does it? For that would mean instant death for sure.

Harry wanted to warn Severus, but he couldn't, for the same reason that Albus Dumbledore couldn't tell Harry before he made the decision to refuse his phoenix.

Severus opened the window, and gazed at coming fire.

The golden phoenix entered, letting out a piercing cry.

COME!

The bird of light and fire said, and everyone in the room understood.

The black-haired man stared at his phoenix, opened his mouth, and closed it again.

Harry dearly hoped that the bird wouldn't fly away when it heard some completely reasonable statement such as "I need to get a spacesuit and a space capsule first".

Severus took in a deep breath, and said: "Let's go to Baikonur Cosmodrome and get start with the preparation."

The phoenix grabbed Severus' shoulder, and they both disappeared in flames.

All parts of Harry was screaming: What? That's unfair! I only asked my phoenix to wait for six months, and it left! Did I just need to say that "let's get a preparation that may last six month going" to retain my bird?

-And by the way, why was there no bird coming to Hermione before she went to Azkaban? I didn't even tell her that she had a horcrux back then! Is it just because she knew she had unicorn blood in her, and she was less likely to die? Or is it because I turned down my bird for the same mission? Is there a one phoenix per mission thing?

Judging from Hermione's expression, she was probably thinking along the same line.

In the semi-interposed space of Lady Rowena Ravenclaw's chamber, amongst mountains and mountains of trash, at the back of the Mirror of Noitlov, Lord Salazar Slytherin had a wide grin on his face.

-Yes, phoenixes are indeed from the Mirror. And as for my two guesses - one, the Atlanteans have a preference for people to explore other stars; or two, you have to believe you have a more than seventy-five percent of chances to die - either one of them, or both of them, must be true. Too bad that I can't test these two separately this time.

Chapter 50: Space Travel Pt VII, Domestic Problems

1:13 pm, July 24th, 1993 (London time)

Harry had a very wide smile as he emerged in Stella's phoenix flames together with Hermione and Severus in his headquarter office. He had just had the greatest book raid ever - Severus had just led them for a tour to the British Library. With the help of Severus, Mad-Eye, three Auror trios, a number of bewitched Muggle librarians, and several duplicated Stones, they now had an extended library with approximately eight hundred thousand books on mathematics, physics, chemistry, material science, biology, medicine, engineering, psychology, history, linguistics, and archeology, among other fields. According to Severus' and Mad-Eye's estimates, the duplicated Stone could at least stabilize the duplicated non-magical books for a couple dozen years.

For the past five hours, the adult wizards duplicated shelves and shelves of books, while Harry and Hermione were responsible for pointing out which subject they needed to duplicate, applying the duplicated Stone on the duplicated shelves, and transferring the duplicated shelves into the many trunks they brought there. Harry and Hermione had wanted to duplicate more books - they hadn't even got anywhere near the science fictions region yet. However, all the adults - including Severus, who had a phoenix to sustain him - had shown signs of magical exhaustion by 1 pm, and the three Auror trios had already drank several bottles of magic-replenishing potions, so they had to come back for security reasons.

Although not completely satisfied, for you could never have enough books, Harry had already rated today among one of the top ten days in his life.

After landing, Harry turned around and cheerfully thanked Severus: "Professor Snape, thank you so much! Duplicating the British Library - this is one of the top fifty most brilliant ideas that I ever know."

Severus smugly smiled, and tilted his head.

Harry noted to himself that Severus seemed to enjoy praises, and exclaimed happily: "Now we can continue our work on the space stuff with answers in almost any field of Muggle science. After Draco, my father and Hermione's parents get here, I guess we can start again."

As house-elves began to serve them with lunch, and Harry started working on the fireplace, Severus used this time to test Hermione on the written Parseltongue they had learned yesterday. "Miss Granger, please use this time to write down the all letters of Parseltongue in the correct order."

When Hermione began to draw the snake-like letters, Harry had a strange feeling. This was one of the few times that Harry had learned things faster and better than Hermione did. For Harry and Draco, the twenty-eight letters of Parseltongue seemed something resembling Greek letters, which were definitely different from the English letters, but not that difficult to learn or to recognize. Once they knew the letters, to spell out Parseltongue words and sentences according to a number of simple phonetic rules felt like a breeze - Parseltongue didn't even have any letter or combination of letters that should be pronounced differently under different circumstances. However, for Hermione and Mad-Eye, it was another story. Harry had already tried to teach Hermione Parseltongue before this, but even with Hermione's advanced auditory system, she still said that all the hisses sounded almost identical to her. As for the written form of Parseltongue, although Hermione's memory was better than anyone Harry knew, the Parseltongue letters still looked like doodling and sprawling snakes to her. She could remember the shapes of the letters that Severus wrote down, but if the same letters written by Harry and Draco were presented to her, or if Severus wrote down the letters again a little bit differently, it was still hard for her to recognize them. As for poor Mad-Eye, Harry couldn't help but to feel sympathy for the old Auror who seemed to prefer dueling Voldemort than learning Parseltongue.

When Hermione was one-third of the way done with the letters, Mad-Eye appeared in the green flames, followed by Dad and Draco. Mad-Eye nodded to Harry, and disappeared in the flames again, probably going to the Grangers.

Dad exchanged greetings with Severus, nodded to Hermione who was struggling with some letters, and the delightly asked: "How is your day, Harry?"

Harry could see that Dad's mood was better than he had been for quite a while. It seemed that having a student again, even if it is just Draco for a few hours, had done a lot of good to Professor Michael Verres-Evans .

Hufflepuff sadly said: You know, we should have thought of this earlier. We shouldn't wait until Hermione and we were discussing about the trajectories of satellites, while Draco knew little about Newtonian physics to think of it. We should have cared more about Mom and Dad earlier.

Slytherin untimely suggested a possible explanation: I know why we did it - until yesterday, we didn't think Mom and Dad as someone useful. As a matter of fact, for the most part of the past year, we were trying to keep everyone away from Muggle science, just in case some idiot would consider transfiguring antimatter as a good idea.

Harry hid his thoughts from the surface of his persona, and happily answered: "One of the best days ever!"

"Really? Should you tell me about even this?" Dad joked.

Actually, we shouldn't. We need to let Mad-Eye erase this part of his memory afterwards. Slytherin said.

Harry knew Slytherin was right to a certain extent, but the Harry under the mask couldn't help but to feel overwhelmed by a wave of sorrow. On the surface, Harry grinned and answered: "You bet."

Dad laughed, as if this little bit of sharing of his son's life was enough for him.

Hufflepuff almost cried: What have we done?!

"Harry, I think you should let more of your friends learn science, or is that prohibited as well?" Dad jokily said, and nodded to Severus, "Young Mr. Malfoy and I had quite a delightful morning. And your godson is quite a bright and charming young man, Professor Snape."

Draco smiled with a hint of shy and awkwardness, as a proper thirteen-year-old should do.

Harry could see that Draco had won Dad's heart within a few hours - Dad even began to praise Draco to his godfather, instead of showing off Harry, but -

Wow, see how good Draco is at satisfying Dad's desire for a "normal" child prodigy? If he is not useful for other stuff, we can at least use him to entertain our parents. Slytherin commented.

Severus' smile was quite sincere as he replied, "Thank you, Professor Verres-Evans. Your son is the most extraordinary young man that I have ever known."

Harry still had some problems with this kind of "normal" talk between guardians of child prodigies. However, he was way better at controlling himself by this point, and he decided that he could at least indulge Dad this much. As for Severus Snape, that man probably had little idea about how to actually raise a child, but he had enough experience talking to his students' parents. And being an extraordinary Legilimens, Severus definitely knew what most parents wanted to hear.

-And Severus probably wants to secure Draco's position, just in case that he dies in space exploration.

At this time, the ultimate nightmare that represented disastrous "normal" parenting appeared in green flames in the form of Roberta and Leo Granger. The very idea that he might end up with them as his parents-in-law could crush most of Harry's romantic thoughts about Hermione at a time of this.

In a brief moment, Harry regretted having including Dr. and Dr. Granger in this project, but Slytherin quickly reminded him that Dr. Roberta Granger was the only one who had some scientific upbringing and could understand Russian. Spending her youth years in the turbulent 1960s in Cambridge meant that Roberta had once been a fan of Trotsky. Harry supposed, he should be grateful that Roberta grew out of it after graduation, and she didn't end up like the Cambridge Five.

Moreover, Hufflepuff demanded: We have already caused them enough worries. If Hermione can deal with their parenting, we can deal with it as well.

Slytherin agreed: Just eat your sandwich, and let them have small talks with Severus and Draco. Draco is an expert in entertaining idiots in the way they prefer, so they will be less troublesome to us.

After Mad-Eye finished applying privacy and security charms around them, and Severus had given a perfect grade on Hermione's recitation of Parseltongue letters (which led to some horrible gloating from Leo Granger), Dad became Harry's hero: "So, what is this thing that you need our help, and then erase our memories with?"

-Oh, Dad, I love you so much.

Harry gratefully began his explanation about their plan for space travel. Of course, he just mentioned that by going to the Moon, they might reduce the interference between magic and Muggle electronics, and conveniently omitted anything about the Interdict of Merlin.

Dad's eyes sparkled and he laughed when he heard about this morning's raid of the British Library. It seemed like Dad would like to become best pals with Severus within the next second. Somehow, this effect was lost on Dr. and Dr. Granger.

To Harry's great relief, the part that Severus was going to the Moon was enough of an excitement to Dr. and Dr. Granger, which proved that their Muggle science education hadn't completely failed. Harry briefly wondered if they would be this excited when they knew that Harry's first choice of wizarding astronaut was actually their daughter. However, Harry found that he had gotten so much better at controlling his tongue than he was one and a half years ago.

"Dad, could you help us figure out a proper landing spot on the Moon?" Harry asked, and then turned to Dr. and Dr. Granger, "Uncle Leo, would you try to figure out how the life support system works in the spacesuits? And maybe also try to figure out how much oxygen, water and other things we need. Aunt Roberta, there are quite some plates in Russian on the space capsule, and I am afraid Professor Snape is not familiar with the technological terms, would you two work on that?"

Leo Granger gave Harry a strange look, as if wondering why Harry, instead of Severus or Mad-Eye, was giving the order.

-Oh, right, I haven't established my dominance in front of the Grangers, and Hermione probably has a hard time conveying this idea to them as well.

Dad became Harry's savior again, as he happily answered: "Of course!"

To Harry's relief, Dr. Leo Granger hesitantly followed suit with a nudge from his wife.

Chapter 53: Space Travel Pt X, Expansion

8:50 am, July 27th, 1993

In Harry's headquarters office, Harry observed the ex-Lord Malfoy who was again "brought back to give testimony", and estimated how much influence this man would have on Severus Snape as the blond continued to speak: "Lord Potter, there is another matter that I have to report to you. According to the Russian guard whom I recently bribed, Grindelwald spoke to Dimitrov in private three times in the recent two days. I think they are up to something, maybe an escape plan, or something more sinister in nature. I think Grindelwald might be trying to show us that if we don't agree to his request, he will make it happen anyway."

-Great. Now, not only the second most powerful dark wizard in the world is planning an escape, but also his accomplice may or may not be Voldemort.

Harry sighed inwardly. He would really like to spend all his time on the space stuff, but there were always so many petty squabbles between human beings that might lead to instant world destruction. And Harry's current deadline for gaining power that most wizards could understand was in the middle of September, when Grindelwald would receive his Stone treatment. Harry dearly hoped that Severus' trip to the Moon would result in something on how to save Dumbledore from Time. Otherwise, Harry would have to either come up with some new schemes against the "nice (aka, less predictable)" Voldemort, or rely on Lucius' probably-not-that-reliable diplomatic skills until someone on their side became a top wizard.

"Mr. Malfoy, if Grindelwald escapes, and in the worst case, allies with You-Know-Who, who can help us?" Harry asked.

It seemed that Lucius had already thought of this matter, for he immediately answered: "Lord Potter, I am afraid that the rest of the world has some misconceptions on the potential danger of our enemies, and they also wonder what we can do. I suppose, if we continue our current policy, the majority of the top wizards in the world would hold back their hands and watch, as what they had done in the late seventies and early eighties. They would very much like to let the two most notorious dark wizards rob the Stone from us, and then they themselves would become the hero who save the day, and study the Stone and the Mirror as a reasonable reward for their great contribution for humanity. Of course, unless we promise a limited number of them that they and they alone can have the privilege to study the origin of magic while others cannot. Lord Potter, if you desire the later approach, I have a list of names who have reasonable good reputations for your consideration."

Harry sighed: "Mr. Malfoy, please write down the names, and their advantages and disadvantages, and I would have a background check on them."

"Lord Potter, there might be something about the majority of the top wizards that could be a good news to you." Lucius' face twisted into a bitter smile. "If the rest of the world knows who has the Stone, the holder of the Stone would have to share its service with wizards around the world - I don't suppose anyone dares to face the wrath of the entire world."

-Err, OK, this IS actually a good news for humanity. The problem is, we don't know what would happen if someone who is NOT that rational becomes the holder of the Stone.

Harry supposed, he needed another alternative plan, but he couldn't think of anything safe. "Mr. Malfoy, please keep thinking what other alternatives we have. And there is another matter that I need to tell you, so that you can ponder on its implications."

Harry observed Lucius closely, and then revealed the space mission to Lucius, with the potential danger exasperated a little and the part about Baikov omitted. As Harry had expected, Lucius showed shock, excitement, and also concern after he heard that Severus would be the astronaut. Harry knew Lucius could be an amazing actor if he wanted to, but Harry thought the concern for Severus' life was real to a certain extent.

After flattering on how smart and creative Harry was (Lucius was really good at this), Lucius said: "If Severus can find anything that may save Dumbledore from Time, then most problems we have will be solved. If there is only regular Interdicted magic in our collection, and the news about this mission leaks -" Lucius' face turned a bit whiter, "Then, we - or at least Severus - will be in graver danger."

Harry was temporarily confused, and then he realized: Capturing and torturing Severus for information wouldn't be that dangerous or hard as robbing the Stone, and it surely wouldn't cause the same level of wrath and endless hunting from the rest of the world. And in Severus' folly, he has leaked the information to Baikov. On another hand, since Lucius can think of the danger Severus would be in so quick, the ex-Lord Malfoy must care about Severus a lot. Moreover, Lucius is indeed genuinely quick on dark things.

Just as Harry was considering how to reveal the Baikov matter to Lucius, the blond wizard continued: "However, even if this mission fails to provide us instant security, it might be a way to solve a long term problem." Lucius hesitated a bit.

"What is it?" Harry asked.

Lucius delivered another matter that Harry hadn't thought of before he provided the service of the Stone to the world: "A side effect caused by the Stone is the blockage of the upward mobility of the youth. Even before the Stone, the problem has been there in the wizarding society. For example, Madam Griselda Marchbanks became a member of the Wizengamot at the age of one hundred and twenty-one, after her father passed away at the age of one hundred and fifty-seven. And now, since Madam Marchbanks has regained her youth, her eldest son may never become a member of the Wizengamot."

"Oh, that." Harry already knew a plan to solve that problem, "We can give a term to Wizengamot seats and any other posts like that, something like you can't serve more than x years in a y year period."

Lucius raised an eyebrow, as if asking Harry, how long Harry's leadership term would be.

-Err…

To be honest, Harry wanted to lead the humanity forever, which meant that Harry would become the one who blocked the way for others. Harry didn't really want to imagine the horrible scene where Harry was fighting with someone who was as smart as Harry for power. However, if the time scale was long enough, this someone would eventually turn up.

Hufflepuff wanted to assign a term for their own leadership, but Slytherin was against the idea: Hey, we need to make sure that the humanity is safe, right? We may never fully anticipate where the danger might come from. And if it suddenly comes, and we are not the Leader, we may not have the authority and resources needed to stop the danger. According to Prophecies, we are the only hope humanity has, remember?

Excuse! Gryffindor roared.

Ravenclaw said: I think we just need to know all the important knowledge. With knowledge, comes power. And that's enough for me.

While Harry was debating in his own mind, Lucius continued as if the eyebrow was raised for nothing: "If we can expand to other planets, there would be a lot of opened vacant seats, and the problem is partially solved."

Slytherin thoroughly agreed: Yes! We can send the young aspirants to far-away galaxies, or even other universes, so that they won't fight for power with us.

Although Harry knew Hermione would scream at him for this, he still felt a bit relieved upon the prospect that he could hold the power for a tad longer, and -

-In the name of Atlantis, the Malfoys are really good at serving their Lords.

I apologize for such a long time without an update. In the past year, I failed to win the H1-B lottery for the second time. For those who don't know, H1-B is a type of working visa to legally work in the US, and you have to enter a lottery in April to have a chance to get it. The chance of winning was ~30-50%. And since I failed twice and expired my OPT-allowed working period, I had to go back to China.

As a matter of fact, I am quite lucky to be from China, where there are quite some job opportunities where my knowledge and skills obtained during my PhD and postdoc years are highly valued, and my US-earned PhD would help me to move up the work-place ladder quicker. I know in a lot of parts of the world, not only there is practically no such position available, but also hard to survive for most people.

Chapter 54: Space Travel Pt XI, Loyalty Problem

11:09 am, July 27th, 1993

In the Boy-Who-Lived's headquarter office, Lucius watched as Mad-Eye Moody disappeared in green flames to do background checks on the list of top wizards that Lucius provided. Lucius hoped this mission could keep the old Auror busy for a while. And as the Boy-Who-Lived and the Girl-Who-Revived went to the newly conjured neighboring room to do some experiments, there were just Severus and Lucius left in this headquarter.

Lucius looked at Severus, who was noting down numbers on the experiment of how much "oxygen" Stella consumed while resting in a sealed transparent box. Lucius didn't quite know what to do with his best friend.

When the Boy-Who-Lived told Lucius about the whole Baikov matter, Lucius was almost speechless at the lack of tactfulness on Severus' part.

The lack of loyalty exhibited in Severus' dealing with Baikov wasn't a problem for Lucius at all - Lucius himself wasn't that loyal to the Boy-Who-Lived, either. He served this new Light Lord because he didn't want the world to end, and because he wanted Draco to secure his position in the new power structure. To be honest, if there was another powerful lord who could ensure the safety of the world, Lucius had no problem switching his loyalty again.

However, the lack of true loyalty to a leader didn't mean that you let the leader knew about it before you could kick your previous master to hell; especially, you shouldn't let your current master knew about it before you even get yourself a new one. And Severus, in his naivety and stupidity, had exactly done that.

-In the name of Merlin, how did Severus Snape survive serving both the Dark Lord and Albus Dumbledore?

-Or does Severus think that he will die in the Moon mission, so he simply doesn't care? And that's why Severus has a phoenix on his shoulder now.

This hypothesis brought quite some horror to Lucius' heart. Lucius knew that Severus was the most powerful wizard that he could cling to, and both the length of his prison sentence and the level of privilege that he would have in Nurmengard depended on Severus. Strangely, Lucius found himself caring about Severus' life for reasons beyond that. Lucius knew true life debts might lead to unknown bonding between the two parties involved, and Lucius had almost lost count on how many life debts he owed Severus. Moreover, Severus had treated Draco and Lucius with friendship and loyalty that Lucius didn't quite expect and couldn't repay in the foreseeable future. Now, Lucius found himself caring that mannerless halfblood more than he had realized, at the time that he might lose him. Suddenly, Lucius was glad that Severus made a deal with Baikov behind Potter's back - the Boy-Who-Lived might veto the deal for security reasons, and Mad-Eye would surely object this deal with all means possible.

However, this didn't mean Severus had to do it so tactlessly - Lucius could name hundreds of ways to make the whole matter look better in the eyes of the Boy-Who-Lived. He really needed to teach the halfblood some maneuver.

An hour ago, under Potter's inquiry, Lucius could only let the Light Lord know that Severus had problems seeing dangers unless it was imminent.

-What else can I say? Severus showed disobedience because he thought he would probably die? Or Severus doesn't want to die, but you might veto his plan to increase his chances of survival?

Lucius didn't assume the Boy-Who-Lived was satisfied with his answer, for now he was left alone with Severus. Potter didn't exactly ask Lucius to help him align Severus' loyalty, but the indication was clear enough.

Lucius pondered his words, and then asked: "Severus, how dangerous is the Moon thing? Muggles went there and came back alive, right?"

The black-haired man started warding the place. After Severus was done, the black-haired wizard sighed, "I have no idea, Lucius. Both Americans and Soviets had tried to send wizards to the space by Muggle rockets, and both wizards were killed. We are trying to do it with magic."

"Severus, my brother -" Lucius let emotions run into his vocal cords, and heard his own voice tremble.

Severus sat down across the table from Lucius, and briefly avoided Lucius' eyes: "I am sorry, Lucius. If I were to know that I may make Draco lose someone again, I - I probably wouldn't be so close with him."

Lucius was a bit baffled by Severus' train of thoughts, but he quickly replied: "Oh, Severus, you don't need to worry about this. Or if you have to, just come back safely."

Severus smiled bitterly: "Lucius, I am truly sorry that my certain actions had put you and Draco into a hard position, I should have been more thoughtful."

This sentence from Severus horrified Lucius: Does he really expect himself to die?

Lucius tried to smile, and proudly announced: "Severus, you don't have to worry about us, we are the Malfoys."

Severus looked at Lucius as if looking at some naughty but cute kid, which annoyed and horrified Lucius on some unspeakable level.

-Why is he looking at me as if I am a child asking for icecreams? This isn't a good sign.

The black-haired man then smile: "Lucius, I've started to feel all the petty squabbles between normal wizards quite pathetic, and I don't care about those things that much. For example, the rivalry between me and Mad-Eye, it wouldn't even be there if either of us wields real power."

Lucius' jaw slightly dropped. He didn't expect this from Severus. He knew wizards like Grindelwald cared more about the origin of magic than an unpleasant Unbreakable Vow, but Grindelwald still cared about mundane matters enough to start a war.

-If Severus feels the rivalry between normal wizards pathetic, then what use can the Malfoys be to him?

Severus rubbed his temple, and smiled with some self-deprecation: "Yeah, who am I to say such things? I am not a Lord, - at least, not in five to ten years. However, when I heard Oleg Baikov talking about his suicidal plan to Apparate multiple times to the space, just for a chance to know whether the Interdicts could be bypassed, and to be able to read Comrade Shakhov's collection of notes, I was really moved, and let my judgement slip." Severus blushed a little, and sighed, "Now, I know I should think more."

-Oh, Merlin, Severus wouldn't take this Baikov as his new best friend, would he?

Lucius suddenly felt his position as Severus' best friend shaken. He needed to formulate a rescue plan, fast.

Lucius was glad that they didn't conduct this conversation in Parseltongue, for he was saying "Severus, I understand", while as a matter of fact, Lucius didn't quite understand this mentality. "However, you need to be careful, and you need to remind Baikov to be careful as well."

Then, Lucius began to exaggerate the danger that Severus might face after he came back alive, in case the news of his mission got out.

This time, it was Severus' turn to drop his jaw. Obviously, before this point, the black-haired Lord-wannabe hadn't thought of that possibility at all.

Now, Lucius began to understand why all the top wizards he knew cared about mundane matters: Those who didn't care about such matter were all killed before they got a chance.

Lucius had to prevent his eyes from sparkling: Merlin, this can be my position to Severus! Oh, and my position in the world, too! Hmm, Draco and his Lord are friends, and I should learn how to serve a Lord who is also my friend as well. It would be ideal that if Draco's Lord and my Lord are allies.

For the ex-Lord Malfoy, helping a potential new lord who was currently in alliance with the Light Lord that both of them were serving didn't even constitute betrayal. Lucius was pretty sure that he could still claim his loyalty to the Boy-Who-Lived in Parseltongue, but he had to check on it in private.

Lucius fought down his impulse to smile, and started selling his service at mundane matters to the black-haired wizard who had twice defeated a Comrade-to-be.

Chapter 56: Space Travel Pt XIII, Draco's Position

Many thanks to Kuilin and Dan, who helped edit this chapter, and saving this story.

9:56 am, July 30th, 1993

Beside the newly named and magically enlarged "Star Lake" in Malfoy Grange in Wiltshire, Draco watched keenly as the modified space capsule disappeared in phoenix fire. Draco hoped that Godfather would have a soft landing in his farm in Nevada, United States. According to the plan, Godfather would go to Nevada, check on how the landing went and equipment worked, tie himself up in the space capsule again, and come back.

Draco then turned his eyes towards Harry, Hermione, Harry's Dad, and Hermione's parents, who were in some heated discussion that Draco couldn't even understand half of. Draco supposed, he should make himself useful in the discussion now. However, his heart wasn't quite in it.

Draco could feel that his position as the right-hand man of the new Light Lord had become more marginalized ever since this space mission came up. Draco knew very well why this mission could be the most important thing that wizards have ever done after the Interdict of Merlin, but the fact that he couldn't understand much of it made Draco feel rather insecure.

Moreover, Harry had been talking about re-organizing the Order of Phoenix, and recruiting new blood. If Draco had really been Number Two or Number Three in a group of ruling elites that he could understand, this would be a great opportunity for him to grasp more power. Unfortunately, Draco was faced with the challenge of "making rules for a modern ruling organization". And what was worse, Draco had little authority over anyone in their current core conspiracy: Harry was his Lord, Hermione was the Lady, Mad-Eye wanted to throw him into Nurmengard, Severus was his Godfather, and Father was, well, Father.

-OK, to be fair, after talking with Father, Godfather has agreed to consult with me on political matters if Father's advice is not available. Somehow, I have a feeling that Godfather is only doing this so that Father and I won't be in a difficult position, while he himself doesn't care much about what Harry thinks. No matter what, Godfather is still the most powerful wizard in our small conspiracy, and he is the one to go on the greatest mission in wizarding history. Therefore, in any power structure that makes sense, Godfather should have privileges, at least, more privileges than me.

Draco remembered a lesson that Father taught him long ago by heart, that Draco should respect people with real powers, be it magic, knowledge, or intelligence. And Father recently said, and Draco agreed, for the safety of the world, they should make sure that everyone respects people with real power as part of the rules which they were helping to make. For whatever weird reason, sometimes, the most powerful wizards in certain societies - such as Dumbledore in Great Britain, and Shakhov in Russia - might make themselves meek servants of the society, and accepted ridiculous rules made by lesser people. Only in societies like that, good-for-nothing bureaucrats such as Fudge and Smirnov could bully powerful wizards around. However, there would always be powerful wizards who didn't like the role of meek and harmless servant - the Comrades had overthrown the Soviet Union, the Dark Lord tried to challenge Dumbledore's orders, and for all Harry's pathetic pretence, the Boy-Who-Lived thought the world should be his own playground.

"Draco, could you come here for a moment?" Harry's voice interrupted Draco's train of thought.

The blond boy showed a bright smile: "Of course."

"Draco, Dad just raised a question that I need to ask you. Do you know if there is anyone who is rumored to be a phoenix animagus?" Harry asked.

Animagus was one of the few fields of magic that Draco grasped better than Harry and Hermione - maybe because their supposed animagus meditation session was interrupted by the house-elf thing, while Draco was the only one who got private lessons on it.

Father had told Draco that the gift of animagus passed down in families, and both the Malfoys and the Blacks had long lists of animagi in the bloodlines. Secretly, Draco thought Godfather's persistence in teaching him the arts of this advanced transfiguration had more to do with Draco becoming one at such a young age. Draco failed to turn into an animagus in his first animagus meditation, for he was unsure whether he should be a dragon or a snake. Ever since Draco could remember, he loved dragons. Draco knew all kinds of dragons in the world by heart when he was three years old, and he always considered the trip that Father took him to the Romanian Dragon Sanctuary when he was six years old as the best vacation. However, no matter what Father said, the man Draco had alway looked up to was a Blue Krait; and for some reason, Godfather also seemed to have a preference for Draco to become a snake. Draco supposed, becoming a snake animagus would make the learning process of Parseltongue like a breath. In his second animagus meditation, Draco decided to choose a snakedragon, which was a rare crossbred between dragons and snakes. That time, Draco successfully adopted an animagus form that had never been recorded in history.

Draco supposed, his rare form of animagus was the reason that Harry asked him the question on phoenix animagus. Draco searched his memory, and answered: "There is no known phoenix animagus. However, Dumbledore's Patronus is a phoenix, and there is some correlation between the Patronus form and the animagus form. Therefore, if Dumbledore were a secret animagus, he is likely to be a phoenix animagus."

Harry replied: "Yeah, we've discussed that possibility. I'll ask Mr. Moody if he knows anything."

Draco briefly regretted his lack of involvement in the discussion among the "scientists", and offered more information as he could: "If you are asking about lores and stories about animagi in general, I think I've heard a bedtime story, where Merlin and an evil sorceress named Madam Mim had an animagus duel, and they turned into many different animals to beat each other. I think both of them seemed to be able to become any animal as they pleased. And in the same story, Merlin could teach King Arthur how to transfigure into both a fish and a bird. Actually, I think there are a number of stories where people could adopt a number of animagus forms."

Harry and Hermione seemed to be excited about this story. Harry asked: "In the rumors, lores, bedtime stories, or anything like that, is there anyone who can become more than one type of animal, say, in the past two hundred years?"

"No, I don't think so." Draco answered.

"Oh." Harry sounded a bit disappointed.

Just as Draco formed the resolution that he should spend more time with Stella, so he might have a chance to become a phoenix animagus to surprise his Light Lord with how useful he was, Harry said to Hermione: "Hermione, maybe you should spend some time with Fawkes, you have the braveness and light in your heart, so you may become a phoenix animagus. - Oh, and Draco, you may have more opportunities to spend time with Stella."

Draco wanted to roll his eyes upon this comment. Two days ago, after Harry concluded that Stella could gain energy from several different types of chemical reactions (Draco wasn't sure what that meant yet), he wanted to try to if Stella could utilize electrical energy. Draco was sure Stella didn't know what the black box named "car battery" was, but she was already quite annoyed by the rocket fuel that Harry fed her. Unfortunately for Harry, Stella partially understood Godfather's reply: "Mr. Potter, if I am not mistaken, things related to electricity don't work well with magic. Therefore, I don't assume the benefits of electrocuting Stella would outweigh the potential risk it brings to Stella."

Although Harry had eventually been convinced by Godfather, Draco thought Stella probably still considered Harry - and by association, his best friend and their parents - as people who wanted to hurt her. Stella had been avoiding the Boy-Who-Lived, the Girl-Who-Revived, and their family members since then.

Draco guessed, he had been useful in telling Harry that he shouldn't try to run the experiments that Stella disliked on Fawkes, for if both phoenixes avoided the Boy-Who-Lived and the Girl-Who-Revived, it would be bad for public relations and become a very negative indicator of their characters in front of potential allies. Draco knew the Boy-Who-Lived could handle political concessions pretty well, but the boy brought up by a Muggle scientist didn't like it when politics hindered the great process of science. However, giving Harry political advice was Draco's value in the core conspiracy, and he had to do the right thing to keep the world safe.

Draco suppressed his impulse to roll his eyes toward the scientists who came up with idea after idea, and shared his experience of becoming an animagus with his Lord and Lady as if nothing had happened: "The animagus meditation potion tastes like some food your potential animagus form likes. For me, it tasted like rare steak. After drinking it, I entered some sort of trance, my vision was both blurred and sharpened -"

A splash of water from the Star Lake broke Draco's sentence.

Everyone turned their head toward the lake. A conical shaped space capsule floated up from the lake, at a position that was two or three meters away from the marked designated point of landing.

A phoenix flame later, the space capsule appeared again on the lakeshore. After a few seconds, the capsule was opened from the inside, and Godfather climbed out with Stella on his shoulder.

Godfather appeared a bit clumsy in the spacesuit. He clicked something, and the back of the spacesuit opened. Godfather climbed out from the back of the hard-shell spacesuit, and said: "As tested previously, with me alone, Stella could land within centimeters of the designated spot. However, when I was strapped into the space capsule, Stella was in her bird space suit, and grabbed her handle inside the capsule, the landing location was no longer that precise. In Nevada, the capsule was 1.9 meters above the ground, and 2.3 meters from the center spot; and for this return trip, the measurement globe said that the bottom of the capsule was 2.4 meters from the water surface, and 2.8 meters from the center of the designated landing spot."

Stella pecked on Godfather's ear, and croaked.

"I know it is difficult." Godfather petted Stella. "We need to practise."

Draco was a bit surprised, for he didn't think Godfather was such a pet person, and Godfather had never shown so much patience for him. During the private sessions, even though Godfather had treated him much better than any Slytherin in the Potion classroom, Draco still had experienced quite some snide remarks.

Godfather wordlessly checked the space capsule for any damage and water leaks, and said: "We need to improve the wand holding sheath on my spacesuit - my wand almost fell out when the capsule hit ground in Nevada. The moisture adjustment charms in it might be malfunctioning, for it felt very dry inside the spacesuit. And by the way, Draco, where did your father get his gloves? I wonder how his gloves can transduce magic so well, while the gloves on the spacesuit can't."

Draco supposed Godfather was also curious in how the snake-headed cane could transduce magic so well. While outsiders were present, Draco only replied: "Twilfitt and Tattings. The Crimp family has been making quality magical accessories for generations. I have quite a few pairs of gloves from them, and I'll have a house-elf bring several pairs here now."

Godfather nodded in thanks, and continued to check on the parts on the capsule loaded with cushioning spells.

Draco noted to himself that he should order several more pairs of gloves for Godfather from Twilfitt and Tattings - actually, he should order two sets of clothing for every occasion from Twilfitt and Tattings for Godfather. Draco quickly summoned parchment and quill from his pouch, and wrote down the orders, and gave the note to his new personal elf, Sparky. On the other hand, Draco dearly hoped that the Malfoys wouldn't become nothing but a deep pocket in their conspiracy.

Then, Harry explained the phoenix animagus idea to Godfather.

Godfather seemed to be quite excited about it, and nodded to Harry's Dad: "Yes, a great idea indeed, Professor Verres-Evans. It would definitely be very handy in space. I should try to see if I am capable of adopting a new form."

Godfather then paused, as if trying to remember something, and then said: "There is another little-written nuance in animagus transformation, that people may be able to transform only part of their body into their animagus forms. It actually comes from the fact that when people change back to their human form after their first successful animagus meditation, most people have some parts of their bodies still in animal forms. It is possible to consciously produce this phenomenon."

Harry opened his mouth, as if he wanted to ask something, but he closed his mouth again.

Draco remembered that Godfather seemed to know what was happening behind him lately. One year ago, Draco had seen Gryffindors silently making nasty gestures toward Godfather behind his back in corridors, but Godfather didn't catch them every time. Draco supposed, Godfather learned or perfected this bat-related trick during the past year, when he was away pursuing power.

"I can teach you all this trick later." Godfather sternly examined the facial expressions of Harry, Hermione, and Draco, and changed the subject with a straight face, "Oh, and the capsule seems to be in good condition from my spells. I'll check for any gas leakage with the Muggle equipment."

Harry pulled out several strange-looking objects that Draco couldn't fully understand from the experimental equipment pouch, and asked."Professor Snape, do you think Stella would be able to haul the entire capsule out from rocks, in case the capsule ended up landing several meters below the ground?"

This was another moment when Draco found himself stupid. Harry's question was quite obvious retrospectively, but Draco had never thought of it, even after the capsule ended up several meters below water.

"Stella, can we give it a try?" Godfather asked.

Stella threw Harry an annoyed look, and cawed in agreement.

And as if getting beaten by Harry's intelligence was not enough, Hermione's father asked another seemingly obvious question: "Professor Snape, I'm still not so sure about how phoenix transportation works. Do we need to check for possible gas loss after phoenix transportation? I mean, when Stella takes the space capsule, does she also take the majority of air inside it? I guess, the capsule not getting soaked when it landed in water was a good sign, but we need to be sure."

Then, everyone with some Muggle science background - which was everyone besides Draco - began planning the improvements needed, and what the next set of experiments should be.

After Draco cooled down a bit from the initial sense of defeat, he found the fact that Hermione's father was able to ask a question that he hadn't thought of was actually good news: Hermione's father isn't as smart as Harry. Therefore, his advantage over me on this kind of stuff must come from learning science.

The young Lord Malfoy silently let out a breath, and decided: I really need to learn Muggle science well. Moreover, I wonder if Muggles have developed the science thing on politics.

Chapter 57: Space Travel Pt XIV, Time Pressure I

I want to thank Dan for beta-ing this chapter.

4:31 pm, August 3rd, 1993

In his headquarter office, Harry sat behind his desk, and practised his confident and soft smile to Mad-Eye: "Mr. Moody, could you take a look at these notes, and see if there is anything that you can read?"

Mad-Eye shot Harry a very suspicious look, as if he wanted to say something, but decided to start flipping through the large stack of duplicates of doodling notes instead.

Harry sighed inwardly for his failed experiment on pretending to lead in another style - Draco had suggested that Harry should at least give it a try.

-OK, I wouldn't be surprised if Mad-Eye suddenly throws several spells at me. Actually, Mad-Eye is probably using wandless and wordless checking charms on me now.

This was another moment when Harry's practise of secrecy, and the distrust between Mad-Eye and Severus, might cost him time. Harry knew some of the notes Mad-Eye was skimming through were things Harry had shown Mad-Eye and Severus while they were trying to figure out how to lock Harry and all the Riddles in Time by the Mirror. Back then, Harry handed over Dumbledore's unreadable notes during the past two years, plus anything in his Line of Merlin heritage that was chronologically near to readable notes containing the concept of "Mirror". At that time, neither Mad-Eye nor Severus claimed that they could understand any magic related to the Mirror from the notes, but neither of them commented on whether they could understand anything else on those notes in the presence of each other. And afterwards, well, Harry let them erase each other's memory.

-I should have asked them separately what they had understood. However, since neither of them felt the need to give me any particular hint to speak to me privately, I guess none of the stuff would be all that important or concerning. Unfortunately, neither of them is very sharp on certain matters.

A certain part of Harry felt pretty good about being the smartest person in their conspiracy, but sometimes, even that part got a bit tired, and he hoped someone else, - say, Hermione, - would catch up with him.

Mad-Eye's hands stopped on a page about one fifth through the stack, and said: "This is Albus' draft years ago, on the techniques of Time-Turner making." Mad-Eye paused, gave Harry a glance, and continued, "I think a number of people in the Department of Mysteries and Aurors who are authorized to investigate crimes related to Time-Turners know how to make a common one, and this improvement doesn't contain any additional layer of Interdicted magic."

Harry's eyes lit up, and glanced at the page again, which still looked like nonsense lines and drawings to him, and he felt a headache upon the ignorance of wizards: Since a bunch of Ministry employees plus probably a number of other people know the secret already, Mad-Eye didn't consider the making of a Time Machine important enough to bring up when we were working on the Mirror!

Admittedly, Severus was present during the whole time, which might mean Mad-Eye did consider this piece of information very important, which would also lead to the conclusion that the mistrust between his two most powerful subordinates was causing him time.

Harry was always up to the challenges of more secrecy, but somewhere in the back of his brain, he felt as if he was missing something - again.

While a significant portion of Harry's brain was trying to figure out the question "what I think I know, and how I think I know it", another part of Harry who worked on autopilot had to ask: "I have already formed several guesses on that. Is it timeless physics? That time is an illusion?"

Mad-Eye was obviously confused by Harry's sentence, but Harry could see the old Auror might have relaxed a bit upon hearing something that was very "Harry".

Harry looked at the page again, which still failed to show any sensible word.

-OK, maybe timeless physics is too advanced for the ancient wizards or witches who invented Time-Turners. Let's go down a bit.

Harry asked again: "Is it that Time is another dimension, similar to Space, and only with a limited capacity for going backwards?"

Harry took a look at the page again, and saw a description in plain English in Dumbledore's handwritings:

"Time is a river that runs downstream, and we only have a limited ability to wade against the flow. After Professor Saul Croaker's improvements on the Hour-Reversal Charm, - very ingenious indeed - we can use cheaper materials such as gold, silver, and quartz to make Time-turners, instead of expensive and rare materials such as mithril and adamantine. I also have some thoughts on the Hour-Reversal Charm, or maybe it should be called Time-Reversal Charm, since the time reversed would no longer be restricted to full hours… "

Although Harry had owned a Time Machine for almost two years now, he was still happy beyond himself to actually know how to make one - and an improved one, no less. Harry always considered it ridiculous that the Time-Turner could only reverse Time in whole hour increments, and it was very unlikely that Time could only be reversed six exact hours. There had been some arguments in magical history books on the inventor of Time-Turners, but all books agreed that it was invented after Merlin, and before the foundation of Hogwarts. From all Harry knew, back then, hours were defined by 1/24 of a day. Although the inventor, -or inventors,- might think differently, it was extremely unlikely that 1/24 of the average rotation cycle of an unimportant planet in a remote area in the Milky Way somehow coincided with one exact quantum amount of Time that could be reversed, and the maximum number of quanta that could be stretched in each twenty-four quanta was exactly six. Harry thought he had read it somewhere that the apparent solar time each day was different every day, and varied from year to year. Even if the maximum Time that could be stretched per twenty-four hours was something like six hours plus one millisecond, Harry would still like to know it, for that might relate to something fundamental for the entire Universe.

Mad-Eye handed that page and three pages after that to Harry, and Harry immersed himself into Advanced Time Machine making.

In the meanwhile, Slytherin noted: hey, Mad-Eye seems to be happy about me showing the notes to him first, and Severus later. If Severus is similar to Mad-Eye on this issue, he may feel alienated. Unfortunately, Severus might not even care anymore.

Harry sighed inwardly. If he were going to form an alliance with some powerful lords and ladies from other countries, he'd better learn how to interact with an ally with an easy case - such as one Severus Snape, who had a phoenix as his proof of character, and could speak only technically true statements if asked in Parseltongue. Moreover, everyone Severus cared about was already sort of in Harry's charge - that man had even handed Harry a small strand of hair from his deceased mother, Eileen Snape when he returned a lock of hair from Lily to Harry a few days ago. Harry knew a certain level of manipulation might have been involved here, he still felt quite personally responsible for everyone in Severus' family, and Harry had strengthened his resolution on reviving every sapient being that had ever lived. As for the thirty-something top wizards in the world, there was no definitive proof of character; there was no guarantee that they would tell even partial truth; not only were their family and loved ones not by Harry's side, they could also be used by dark wizards to force the lords and ladies to stand against Harry; and every one of them could defeat the combined forces of Severus, Mad-Eye, plus a bunch of Aurors.

Harry really resented the potentially grim prospect of having allies who were less intelligent yet more powerful than he was.

From a very dark corner in Harry's mind, a voice quietly suggested a very "creative" idea: Although it is hard to gain a lot of magical power in a short time, it is possible to - well, you know, if we can gather all the top wizards together, and construct a carefully calculated timed antimatter bomb…

Everyone else - including Slytherin - gasped in horror, yelled in righteous fury, and started throwing punches on Dark Harry, for all of them knew it was WRONG, and the disappearance of all top wizards would definitely lead to instant chaos - if not World War III.

Harry decided to shut down his dark mode for as long as possible - or at least until the next crisis really called for it.

Dark Harry sneered.

Just as Harry was trying to get his dark side under control, with a twist in his lips, Mad-Eye, who had been observing Harry for a while, brought out a colored paper copy of a yellowish black-and-white magical photo of - a bearded Severus Snape with a hole in his chest?!

-WHAT?!

Harry's brain wanted to deny the possibility of Severus' death, then the parts that were still functioning as they should realized that the corpse couldn't be Severus Snape: for the sake of Merlin, the photo is too old, and Mad-Eye is too calm.

Although Mad-Eye and Severus fought like cats and dogs everyday, Harry didn't think the no-longer scarred Auror would so calmly show the Boy-Who-Lived a photo of a deceased Severus. The Mad-Eye Moody in Harry's head should be snarling "constant vigilance" and summoning members of the Order of Phoenix to protect Harry and the Stone six hours before he found Severus dead - whether the black-haired wizard was killed by Voldemort, some other dark wizards, or even Mad-Eye himself -

-Unless this isn't Mad-Eye Moody…

As Harry was pretending to be in shock, while inwardly grinding his brain to figure out an escape plan, the man in front of the Boy-Who-Lived snarled with a raspy voice: "Shocked? Me too. I recently did some diggings of the top secrets of the former USSR, and got this rare photo of our old Ivan Pokrov - or at least that's the so-called real name I can get - commonly known as Lord Rasputin, after his death and with all his magical disguises worn off. Well, one can never know enough about dead dark wizards."

Rasputin, oh, of course, the powerful Russian Lord and true seer, would and should change his appearances, and adopt a new identity, before meddling with muggle politics. Harry reasoned. Somehow, his disguise magic failed after his death. But why does Severus resemble him so much?

Harry's imagination was quick in generating a number of explanations for the amazing resemblance, ranging from the most innocent one such as Severus was Rasputin's descendant, to the possibility that Severus was born/made as a magical clone for the purpose of the Russian lord's revival, and to ones that sounded really familiar: as a true seer who had foreseen his own death, Rasputin might have made a horcrux before he was assassinated, and this horcrux somehow wanted to make baby Severus a living horcrux, but the magic botched and imprinted Rasputin's looks and parts of his character on the baby.

Part of Harry really resented the last possibility, for that would mean Harry wasn't that special.

But hey, what you don't like doesn't have to be true. Part of Harry offered. Rasputin was famous for his fondness for any breathing female. Severus might just be his descendant. Before other parts of Harry could sneer, Harry's Ego continued, you know, rumor says the Malfoys jinxed their own bloodline so that all the male descendants would look like their ancestors, which makes a lot of sense when they expect their ancestors to revive someday -

Then Harry got it: Lord Rasputin expected himself to rise again - no, he probably foresaw his own revival.

Harry knew that true seers couldn't remember the Prophecies they told, but this didn't mean they couldn't know through other means. Considering the fact that Merlin threw away his life and magic to make the Hall of Prophecy, which recorded all the Prophecies made in the world, magical sound recording devices must have been invented during or before Merlin's time. And for a cunning true seer like Lord Rasputin, it made a lot of sense for him to carry several such devices with him all the time.

Harry secretly smiled to himself, as this could be a good sign for his plan to revive every sapient being that had lived.

Mad-Eye's next sentences diverted Harry's train of thoughts: "One of the major difficulties of revival through a horcrux is to create a perfect body for oneself. There is no guarantee that your servant would willingly sacrifice his or her flesh after your death, and your father's bone could be tampered with - Snape and I had put quite some interesting stuff to the supposed tomb of Tom Riddle Sr., which obviously didn't serve its due purpose. However, it might not be too difficult for really powerful wizards to put a curse onto themselves and all their descendants, and I am wondering what the so-called Lord Rasputin might have tried in that department."

Mad-Eye's normal eye shifted slightly, as if he was not comfortable implying matters of a certain nature in front of the thirteen-year-old Boy-Who-Lived.

Being a Ravenclaw who had read too many books that he was not supposed to read, Harry had fully understood Mad-Eye's implications. In the back of his mind, Hufflepuff gasped in horror, Gryffindor wanted to track down the evil lord's horcruxes and put all of them in eternal fire, Ravenclaw tried to point out the fact that a male's mitochondria couldn't be passed down to his descendants, but Slytherin sneered and pointed out that Rasputin might have cursed his sisters - if he had them - as well. And in a dark corner, someone suggested that the Russian lord might actually have had kids with his sisters - or even his mother - to maximize his chances of success.

The no-longer old Auror's lips twisted in regret and anger. "I've checked up on Snape when Albus took him under his wings - but not enough, - you can never be vigilant and paranoid enough, as it turned out. There had been a rumor among the pureblood families that Eileen Prince's supposedly maternal grandfather, Serpens Lestrange, was sterile; and her mother, Virgo Prince nee Lestrange, was the illegitimate daughter of some wizard in Europe. I really should have tracked her true grandfather back then, but I was distracted by Voldie and all that. Although I've checked muggle public records, and the earliest record that I could find on the Snape family was in 1918, somehow I failed to make the Russian connection, until the lad gained too much power too quickly after his trips to the former Soviet Union. Albus had always told me to read more Muggle newspapers; if I did as Albus told me, I might have known that the rich Muggles fled Russia several years before Comrade Shakhov ousted his wizarding enemies."

This news should be way more alarming than it was if there was not a phoenix on the shoulder of Severus. Stella was probably a good living proof that Severus had not been occupied by someone's horcrux.

Moreover, there was another question that had been circling in the back of Harry's mind for a while -

"Mr. Moody, what do you think on how you obtained this information?" Harry asked.

Mad-Eye was probably expecting this question, for he quickly answered: "I greased a few palms, and a bunch of memory charms were also involved. But for whether the photo is real - well, I assume everyone with half a brain knows the Snape lad is related to the protection of the Stone, and a number of cunning ones might have noticed the Russian connection. And there it was, an old top-secret photo lying there among piles of old files, waiting for my discovery."

This did sound quite suspicious regardless of whether Severus was indeed a result of a powerful wizard's curse onto his bloodline. If it were true, some ex-Comrade, or some other powerful and cunning wizard or witch who had access to top secrets of the former USSR, might have noticed the resemblance, plus Severus' role in the protection of the Stone, and devised a scheme involving Mad-Eye obtaining the photo; if it were false, well, someone must have faked the photo, and planted it there.

As a matter of fact, there was a test that could prove or disprove the kinship between Severus and Rasputin, one that many wizards probably didn't know about: a DNA test. And if Harry remembered it right, the male part of Rasputin was soaked in Formalin, and on display in a museum - though there was no guarantee whatsoever of its authenticity.

Before Harry could suggest the idea, Mad-Eye drew out another two photos, a magical photo of a sullen looking young witch in silver and green trimmed Hogwarts robes, and an old Muggle mugshot of an angry-looking middle-aged man.

Harry didn't need to read the fine lines on the bottoms of the photos to realize that these were Severus' parents, who both resembled Severus a lot, and more importantly, resembled each other.

"The photo of the young Eileen Prince is less likely to be fake, for many people in the wizarding world knew her, and the memories, photos, and paintings are consistent; as for Tobias Snape, well, at least the memories of the Muggles whom I have checked did not tell me anything differently." Mad-Eye said.

Harry felt a surge of sadness. It didn't take a genius to figure out that Severus' parents were unhappy as a couple, but they didn't choose to divorce, or in Eileen's case, just took their child and went to somewhere that Tobias could never find, for if a clever and evil lord cursed his own bloodline to inbreed according to Prophecies, the same curse would ensure they try to make more babies no matter what.

The only thing that came sort of as a comfort was that Severus had loved Lily for many years, even though Lily didn't return his favor. This meant Severus could still fall in love when the influence of the possible curse was absent.

- On another thought, Severus' ill fate might be determined by Prophecies all along. His birth, for example, was very likely to be one.

- Moreover, Dumbledore probably wrote things on Lily Evan's Potions textbook according to a Prophecy. That act caused a great fight between Severus and Lily, increased the chance for Lily and James' marriage, ensured that Lily knew how to make her sister beautiful, and finally, led to the birth and proper upbringing of Harry Potter.

- Not to mention, Dumbledore had also arranged for Severus to overhear one of the Prophecies, so that particular one would be delivered to Voldemort, the one which would later cause Severus to defect to the Light side.

Hufflepuff suggested sadly: since Dumbledore was definitely acting on Prophecies for matters related to us, we might have wrongly reproached him for using Severus in a harsh way. For if he had relieved Severus' burden of guilt and grief, or ended Severus' infatuation for Lily earlier, there might not be an evil Potions master for us to publically defy, and the other Tom Riddle wouldn't teach us the valuable lesson on how to lose.

Then, Harry's mind helpfully remembered the hysterical laughter that Dumbledore had after Harry blackmailed him: Dumbledore might have just realized why Prophecies demanded an evil Potions master in Hogwarts until that day, and how all the sufferings of both the students and Severus himself served to properly motivate the hero. Moreover, Dumbledore might have already pondered on the comprising solution that Severus left the younger students alone, yet still was abusive towards students in their fifth year and above, for quite some time. There might even be Prophecies about that as well.

Harry wanted to bang his head against his desk. He still had a problem accepting that Time and the Universe worked that way.

On a positive note, Slytherin said, Severus' above-average level of intelligence and magical power might also come from Lord Rasputin. Otherwise, he wouldn't get the chance to become the first wizard to go to the Moon, and possibly bypass the Interdict of Electronics and the Interdict of Merlin. The personal happiness of one particular human being that we happen to know, plus that of a handful of Rasputin's other descendants, plus that of the former students taught by Severus, is just a small price to pay to save every sapient being on the planet, isn't it? Don't forget, our parents' lives have been sacrificed for this goal.

All the reasonable parts of Harry accepted Slytherin's logic, yet he all of a sudden understood the reason Merlin constructed the Hall of Prophecy, so that the ones involved in Prophecies would be aware of their fate: it was simply too sad to be manipulated by Prophecies your whole life without knowing anything.

Harry's Slytherin side split into two parts.

Slytherin Number One sneered: hey, are you sure that your desire to let Severus know isn't because you see the similarity between Severus and ourselves? Dumbledore must have felt guilty about manipulating us to the level of smashing our pet rock, yet that good man was wise enough to keep his mouth shut until his departure. We should do the same.

Just as Hufflepuff and Gryffindor began their protest, Slytherin Number Two offered an effective counter argument: what if Severus runs into a Russian witch, or a female magical creature while he is running all over the former USSR? I can't see how starting a family under the influence of Rasputin's magic could be good for our mission.

Moreover, there is a decent chance that Shakhov would have some notes from Rasputin. Do you want to imagine what Severus might find out while that man was on the Moon? Ravenclaw added.

Slytherin Number One conceded: I don't think Severus is sharp enough to connect himself with Rasputin if he comes across something on how to curse your own bloodline, though it is possible that Shakhov might have left a note or a sketch to be watchful for witches and wizards with a particular look. OK, just the Rasputin part, then.

Harry breathed in, and breathed out. "We have to notify Professor Snape about this."

Author's note:

Alan Rickman was the actor who played Severus Snape in Harry Potter movie series. His performance in Rasputin: Dark Servant of Destiny won him a Golden Globe. My fabrication of the kinship between Severus and Rasputin here was not only a part of the theme on the pursuit of eternal life (through good, not-so-good, and evil means), but also a tribute to Alan Rickman, who passed away in 2016.

Chapter 58: SpaceTravel Pt XV, Time Pressure II

I want to thank Dan for beta-ing this chapter.

5:40 pm, August 3rd, 1993

Harry observed Severus carefully as the black-haired man's knuckles whitened on his wand, his black eyes glittered, and his face twitched and un-twitched.

Stella on Severus' shoulder looked both confused and tense. She looked like she wanted to coo a comforting song, but was silenced by a glance from her master.

Fawkes, who had been summoned by Harry upon Mad-Eye's request, stopped eating chocolate frogs scattered on the small table the moment Mad-Eye pulled out Rasputin's photo and Severus began to tense up. He looked back and forth with his black beady eyes between Mad-Eye and Severus, unable to grasp the rising emotion from the master of the other phoenix.

Harry could feel there was magic building up around the man each time his cheeks jumped, and it was like water rising, rising, and rising, like the gushing Congo River in the rainy season held back by nothing but a thin string pretending to be a dam. The magic didn't exactly go wild, but not going wild somehow became more frightening by the second.

The magical fire burning in the fireplace in Harry's headquarter dimmed and quivered, shuddering as if it, too, was afraid of what might happen if the black-haired wizard lost control over his magic.

Harry had experienced Severus' emotional unrest in close range before, and he had told Mad-Eye to allow Severus time to calm down by himself. However, this time, the magic tensing up around Severus was way more frightening than the time Harry unwisely told Severus why Lily did not forgive him, but offered James Potter forgiveness generously.

Harry racked his brain, trying to figure out something truly wise to say. None of Harry's mentally prepared scenarios matched this level of intensity - the magic in air began to resemble that radiating from Dumbledore when the ancient wizard was in his righteous fury. And apparently, Stella couldn't comfort her master who did not desire comforting.

Harry stole a glance at Hermione, who was definitely better at this sort of thing than Harry, but it seemed that the Girl-Who-Revived didn't have much to say, either.

"Lad -" Mad-Eye began in a sympathetic tone that was quite rare for this rough auror.

"Shut, up!" Severus seethed through his teeth.

Mad-Eye's lips closed at once, and almost before Harry could realize, Mad-Eye's normal eye widened, and his wand was already pointing toward Severus -

Before Harry could do something to stop Mad-Eye and Severus from killing each other - or rather stop Severus from killing Mad-Eye, the black-haired man grabbed Stella, and vanished in a burst of flames.

-Err...

Harry didn't think it would a good idea for Severus to be alone, going who knows where in this emotional state, but he didn't know if getting someone to console Severus would be a good idea, either, for the man might not want his godson or his newly-found best friend to know about his family tree.

This is just the Rasputin stuff. We have not even begun with the other Prophecies, such as the one with the Potions textbook. Have you all seen why Dumbledore kept his mouth shut yet? End your useless moral dilemma, and keep your secrets from now on. Seethed Slytherin. Oh, and by the way, with Severus' intelligence, he might also figure out that he had been manipulated by Dumbledore his whole life on a deeper level than he had known. Guess what, he might even figure this out during his trip to the Moon, and he might conveniently destroy the scrolls containing magic on how to save Dumbledore, and Obliviate himself.

He wouldn't do that! He has a phoenix! Protested Hufflepuff.

Slytherin scoffed: yeah, why are you so sure that Stella won't be convinced by her master, and think that it is for the greater good? Fawkes didn't leave Dumbledore when he purposefully sacrificed our parents.

Then Harry noticed something: Mad-Eye pointed his wand toward his own lips, and cast something.

Harry knew magical children had accidental magical outbursts, but Severus was too old for accidental magic to seal Mad-Eye's lips, or was he?

Harry had always wondered how magic worked. Most spells used in western wizarding society nowadays were in magical pseudo-Latin, while spells taught in magical schools in Asia were in words resembling their own native languages. Therefore, though within a certain pseudo-language system, the exact wording and wand movements did matter, a particular language was not required for magic to serve certain functions, such as stunning someone. Now it seemed that Severus could seal Mad-Eye's lips just by a strong desire without words in the magical pseudo-Latin that the ex-Head of Slytherin had been trained to use.

"If not for Fawkes still liking the lad, I would be sure that he is occupied by Rasputin. Severus shouldn't gain so much power so quickly even if Shakhov and Grindelwald are mentoring him together. I could only somewhat verify Perenelle Flamel's body, though; I am not sure if the heap of ash was actually Master Nicolas Flamel..." Mad-Eye's sound trailed off.

When first hearing of the news on the condition of the Flamels' "bodies", Harry had thought that was because there was actually only one Flamel. However, there might be another possibility: Lady Baba Yaga and Perenelle had really loved each other, so the Dark Lady decided to quit her career, and took on the identity of Nicolas Flamel. And while dueling Lord Voldemort and/or his pawn, the Dark Lady managed to escape, leaving the pretense that there was actually one Flamel. And that was why the senior Tom Riddle thought Perenelle, as a teenage girl, managed to kill Lady Baba Yaga.

-If Lady Baba Yaga is still alive…

-That explained a lot, actually. Lady Baba Yaga probably has some fondness for Hogwarts, so she might kill the acromantulas, plus the dark wizard behind the acromantulas. Moreover, she might teach Lucius the advance shielding charm, not as being particularly kind, but in the same way that she parceled out secrets and powerful magic to Dumbledore when she saw that Lord Voldemort was winning. Just this time, she parceled out one of her secrets to all of us, and Lucius was just a conduit.

-Come to think of it now, the knowledge that the secret of Grindelwald's invincibility and the role of the Death Stick might be from Lady Baba Yaga as well. I might have wronged Severus on this.

-And the matter with Severus. Lady Baba Yaga might want to raise someone again, the same way she raised Dumbledore. And within our small circle of conspiracy, Severus is probably the only one who might have the potential to hold off Voldemort for a while before Hermione or I gain enough power that she could understand. And since Lady Baba Yaga is not arrogant, she might consider me to be too clever, and Hermione to be too moral.

Harry heaved a sigh. This was probably the second time that a really powerful Dark Wizard decided against taking him as an apprentice. He couldn't even tell if this was a good sign.

Just as Harry's Slytherin side and Hufflepuff side began to debate whether he should let Mad-Eye know about Lady Baba Yaga, a bright light ball appeared in the room.

In the ex-Head of Slytherin's tired voice, the patronus said: "Mr. Potter, please let me in your place by phoenix."

Parts of Harry were relieved that he got a good excuse to postpone a decision for a difficult problem.

Harry quickly waved his wand, and allowed Severus to come back. He was glad that Severus managed to calm himself down within, err, six hours or less.

A flame later, Severus was back in Harry's headquarters. His new expensive robes were littered with spots of mud, his black eyes were slightly bloodshot, the wrinkles around his eyes might have grown a bit, and his face was otherwise blank.

Before anyone could say anything, the black-haired man took out a black metal box from his pouch, and handed it to Harry. "Mr. Potter, the box contains locks of hair from my father, my maternal grandmother, and my paternal grandfather. Oh, well, at least I think the bodies in their respective graves are my ancestors'. Please run your scientific test with them, and see if Mad-Eye's theory is true."

-Err…

Harry nodded gravely to the man in distress, and asked: "Is there anything I can do for you, Professor Snape?"

Severus looked as if he wanted to give Mad-Eye a deadly glare, but in his currently exhausted status, it was just a roll of his eyes. Severus sat down on the sofa, and said resentfully: "You may ask Mad-Eye to show some respect by not digging up graves. And by the way, if any of the remaining Lestranges outside prison alert the authorities about the burglary in their family cemetery, you know which Auror to send to conduct this so-called investigation. If I am not mistaken, Mad-Eye probably has already run DNA tests in several Muggle labs. However, ever since I knew about the role father's bones play in a revival ritual, I did some cover-up on the graves of my recent ancestors, and I am glad my work was not completely wasted."

Hermione gasped at the implication, and her brown eyes darted to Harry as if pleading with him to do something, or to prevent something.

Harry didn't remember exactly whether tampering with one's ancestors' graves called for blood or death challenges in the etiquettes of the Most Ancient Houses, but to tamper with fake graves might not require such revenges.

-Or maybe Mad-Eye did find the true graves, and he just did a great cover-up, so Severus wouldn't have an good excuse to kill him for the offence.

-On another thought, maybe Severus did find out that Mad-Eye tampered with the true graves, and he just pretended that he didn't figure this out, so that he would have an excuse not to kill Mad-Eye for family honor - probably not wanting to cause world destruction, or to make it easier to escape punishment after assassinating Mad-Eye. Remember, Severus didn't say it in Parseltongue.

-Oh, great. Now the most powerful wizard in our conspiracy has found a justified reason to kill the second-most powerful one.

Somewhere else, a non-plotting Harry still felt pretty sorry for Severus, for Harry would feel upset if anyone tampered with James and Lily's monuments, let alone digging up their graves without Harry's consent.

Slytherin tried to soothe Harry: hey, we know that is what Mad-Eye has to do. Mad-Eye would definitely ask us if he needs something from our parents' bodies, and he would also ask Minerva for similar matters. Plus, Severus himself and Mad-Eye had put interesting stuff into the supposed tomb of You-Know-Who's father. Tom Riddle, Sr., who was probably innocent, lost protection to his calm in death because of his son's conducts. We considered that act completely justified. Similarly, Severus joined the Death Eaters by his own free will - we have not asked Severus how many people he killed before he defected to the Light, have we? By the same logic, the tampering of Severus' ancestors' graves is just an unfortunate collateral damage as well. Back me up here, Hufflepuff?

Hufflepuff was almost in tears, Gryffindor was in dilemma, while Ravenclaw argued that trying to figure out whether your ally was under a curse did not constitute as good a reason as trying to stop a dark lord from crawling back to life.

Before Hermione in Harry's mind or the real Hermione could say anything, Severus continued: "More importantly, I think Time is pressuring us. We really need to speed up our space travel schedule."

The possible descendant of a true seer sighed, and said to the Boy-Who-Lived and the Girl-Who-Revived in bewilderment: "If the school schedule is similar to the schedule when I was here, the pre-semester staff meeting should be held within two weeks, by which time the professors for the next school-year should be determined. Minerva is begging Lupin to continue teaching Defense class, and she is committing a slow suicide by teaching Transfiguration and being the Headmistress at the same time. In the meanwhile, we have a list of extraordinarily qualified witches and wizards - including Lord Grindelwald - applying for various staff positions. I wouldn't be too surprised if some mishap happens to any of our current staff members before the next semester starts. Even if we are lucky enough to keep all the staff of last school-year, Mr. Potter, I do not want to imagine the scene when Minerva meets Trelawney after the summer break, let alone the many occasions that our beloved Divination Professor would have meals in the Great Hall. And as I now reflect on it, Mr. Potter, Albus might have been actively preventing you from knowing more Prophecies."

Professor Trelawney's hallow icy voice from Harry's first year began to echo in Harry's mind: ""HE IS COMING, THE ONE WHO WILL TEAR APART THE VERY -" And then, Dumbledore dragged Trelawney away in mid-sentence by phoenix fire. And there were also the words in Dumbledore's letters confirming that Harry should not learn more Prophecies.

And this time, the presence of the new phoenix owner himself might trigger a Prophecy.

Harry sighed inwardly. "Yes, we definitely should speed up."